不好意思 对不起 对不起
Excuse me. Sorry. I'm sorry.
不好意思 借过
Excuse me. Coming through.
（新泽西 1984年）
今晚 魔术师莱昂内尔·施莱克
Tonight, so-called magician Lionel Shrike
将通过表演他所说的「不可能的表演」
is making another sad attempt for attention
再次吸引观众们的目光
by performing what he calls an impossible feat.
保险箱是由最坚固的钢铁打造
The safe is made of the strongest iron.
无法被锯断 也不能烧穿
It can't be sawed through or pried.
但莱昂内尔·施莱克依然认为自己能逃脱
Yet, Lionel Shrike thinks he's able to escape.
爸爸 爸爸
Dad! Dad!
嘿 伙计 你来了
Hey, buddy. You made it, huh?
看到那边的座位了吗
Now, see that seat there?
那是全场最好的位置
It's the best seat in the house.
难道莱昂内尔·施莱克真的能从中脱身？
Is Lionel Shrike the kind of magician who can pull this off?
或是他只是脑子进水了？
Or is he actually in over his head?
我们拭目以待
We'll see about that.
- 怎么了 - 我不想让你去
- What's the matter? - I don't want you to go.
迪伦 好了 我们说过的
Dylan, come on. We talked about this.
记得吗？这是我的工作
Remember? This is what I do.
我要证明那些唱反调的人是错的
I got to prove all those naysayers wrong.
好吗？而且…
Okay? Besides…
我每次都会给自己留一手的
I always keep something up my sleeve.
好 跟爸爸对表？
Now, got your watch like your dad's?
- 多少秒？- 300秒
- Okay. How many seconds? - Three hundred.
300秒 可能还要快一些
Three hundred. Maybe a few less.
嗯 我爱你
Mmm. I love you so much.
好 再见 大小伙
Okay. See you later, big man.
女士们先生们 有请莱昂内尔·施莱克
Ladies and gentlemen, Lionel Shrike!
他能够摈住呼吸吗
Will he be able to hold his breath?
他能逃出保险箱吗？
Will he be able to somehow escape the safe?
3 2 1…
Three, two, one…
2 3…
Two, three,
4 5 6 7 8…
four, five, six, seven, eight…
296… 297 298 299 300
296… 297, 298, 299, 300.
303 304…
303, 304…
已经5分钟了
It's five minutes now,
我们还是未看到或是听到 任何莱昂内尔·施莱克的动静
and we have not seen or heard anything from Lionel Shrike yet.
让开
Move!
爸爸
Dad!
爸爸 爸爸
Dad! Dad!
放开我
Let go of me!
爸爸
Dad!
不 爸爸
NO! Dad!
爸爸 放开我
Dad! Let go!
找到他
Find him!
眼睛
The Eye.
也许不会说谎
It may not lie…
但别以为它不能被谎言蒙蔽
But don't think for a moment that it can't be lied to.
所见即所信
Seeing is believing.
但那是真相吗？
But is it truth?
人们把骑士当做高贵的罗宾汉 他们是吗？
People see the Horsemen as noble Robin Hoods. Are they?
还是他们只是普通的贼？
Or are they common thieves?
这要看你从哪个角度去看
Depends on your point of view.
你只知道 他们从拉斯维加斯的舞台上
Here's what you know.
抢劫了一家位于巴黎的银行
They robbed a bank in Paris from a stage in Las Vegas.
他们从一个保险巨头身上
They fleeced an insurance magnate
卷走了数亿美元
of hundreds of millions of dollars
然后在纽约的一个屋顶上消失了
and disappeared from a roof in New York.
总是让最忠诚的支持者 沐浴在金钱之中
Always showering their devoted fans with money.
接下来是你不知道的
Here's what you don't know.
他们留下了一个人
They left one man behind.
他被关了起来 替他们背黑锅 那就是我
Framed. Holding the bag. Me.
你们在听吗 骑士们
Are you listening, Horsemen?
一旦你们出现 你们愿意
When you emerge, and you will,
我会等着你
I will be there waiting.
记住我的话 你会遭到报应的
Because mark my words, you will get what's coming to you.
以你想象不到的方式
In ways you can't expect.
但绝对是你应得的
But very much deserve.
因为我相信一件事 以眼还眼
Because one thing I believe in is an eye for an eye.
《惊天魔盗团2》
（地铁 往曼哈顿）
欢迎 丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Welcome, Daniel Atlas.
哪位跟我讲话？
Who am I speaking to?
我想看天眼的幕后者
I asked to see the face behind all of this.
你问了很多问题 而且满腹牢骚
You've asked many questions. And registered many complaints.
放心 我们都听到了
You can rest assured that we've heard you.
有吗？因为我不…
Have you? Because I don't…
- 信任？- 不
- Trust? - No.
你的领袖？你手下的骑士？
Your leader? Your fellow Horsemen?
也许是我们？
Perhaps even us?
我讨厌我们已经隐姓埋名生活了一年
I don't like that we've been living in hiding for a year.
我不喜欢每次听到迪伦的消息 内容都是
I don't like that every message I get from Dylan is,
「等待 要耐心 天眼自有计划」
"Wait. Be patient. The Eye has a plan."
等待 要耐心
Wait. Be patient.
天眼自有计划
The Eye has a plan.
这是个游戏 我不想玩了
This is games and it's not working for me.
你觉得应该是你来带领骑士们 而不是迪伦
You feel it is you who should be leading the Horsemen, not Dylan.
如果那就是你要的 那就坚持下去
If that is what you desire, stay the course.
相信你独特的能力
Trust that your unique talents
伟大的思想不会被埋没
and remarkable mind will not go unrecognized.
我们有个新任务给骑士们
We have a new mission for the Horsemen.
迪伦有个计划 而且很快就会召唤你
Dylan has a plan and will gather you together soon.
现在离开这
Now leave!
（联邦调查局 司法部门）
北卡罗来纳 佛罗里达 马里兰 缅因
…North Carolina, Florida, Maryland, Maine.
整个东海岸都包括了
We're talking the entire eastern seaboard.
我需要看到结果
I need to see some results.
噢 嘿 抱歉
Oh, hey. Oh, sorry.
稍微打扰一下 能占用你们几分钟吗
Just real quick. Can I have you for a couple of minutes?
我正在忙 迪伦
I'm right in the middle of something, Dylan.
我知道 没事的 嘿 大伙儿 抱歉 抱歉打扰了
No, I know. It's okay. Hey. Hey, everybody. Sorry. Sorry about that.
打电话给市长
Call the mayor.
非常感谢 双胞胎？不错
Thanks a lot. Twins, huh? Good.
他也来吗
Is he coming?
好吧 要不是非常重要的事
Look, I wouldn't have brought you out of that meeting
我也不会打断你的会议
unless it was something important.
是关于骑士们的
It's about the Horsemen.
这里有事情发生了 而且现在正在发生
Somethings happening here and it's happening now.
网络留言板上 精英魔术团体
Message boards. Elite magic society.
里面有关于骑士的讨论
There is chatter going on about the Horsemen
而且和奥克塔有关 软件巨头
and something happening with Octa, the giant software company.
我知道奥克塔是什么
I know what Octa is.
对不起 女士 但两个月前
I'm sorry, ma'am, but two months ago
我们派人去费城了 就因为他自以为知道…
we sent men to Philadelphia because he knew…
- 我说了那次我错了 - 他知道骑士们
- And I said that I was wrong. - He knew that the Horsemen
会攻击欧洲大西洋银行峰会
were going to hit the Euro-Atlantic Banking Summit.
- 我有证据 - 让他说完
- I have proof. - Let him talk.
谢谢 通讯往来
Thank you. Communications.
我认为其中一方是丹尼尔·阿特拉斯
Contact between who I think might be Daniel Atlas
另一方很可能是梅里特·麦金尼
and who may be Merritt McKinney.
你有什么证据 电子邮件 手机 有手稿吗？
And what do you have? Emails? Cell phones? Any transcripts?
- 鸽子 - 什么？
- Pigeons. - What?
对不起 你是说鸽子密探吗？
I'm sorry, you mean stool pigeons?
不 我说的就是鸽子 真正的鸽子 就像信鸽那样
No, I mean actual pigeon pigeons. Like carrier pigeons.
- 好吗？魔术师变戏法都用的信鸽 - 白鸽
- Okay? Magicians work with pigeons. - Doves.
听我说
Stay with me.
这里有只鸽子
This pigeon, right here…
这是丹尼尔·阿特拉斯 同一只鸽子
There's Daniel Atlas. Same pigeon.
东村
East Village.
同样的鸽子 西村
Same pigeon, West Village.
42大街 鸽子 65大街
42nd Street, pigeon. 65th Street.
一直到乔治·华盛顿大桥
All the way up to the George Washington Bridge
跟一个和梅里特·麦金尼长得一模一样的人
on a sail boat with a guy that looks just like Merritt McKinney.
这一切有什么含义？
And what does this all mean?
我知道那意思是什么 没有任何含义 都是瞎扯
I know what it means. It means nothing. It's bullshit.
- 你能换个调调吗 - 不行
- Could you sing a new song? - No.
那次呢 两年前你差点…
How is it that two years ago you were so close…
你认为我独自行动就是为了 毁掉我自己的调查吗
You think I went out of my way to screw up my own investigation?
你认为我是大白痴？
You think I'm that big of an idiot?
你自以为很聪明
You know what I think now? I think you're smart,
但其他所有人都认为你是蠢货
but you want everybody else to think that you're an idiot.
好了 住口
Okay, stop.
考恩 虽然我是新来的 但我看得出来
Cowan, I know I'm new here, but as far as I can tell,
连根本不认识你的人都觉得 你是个混球
people who don't even know you, think you're an asshole.
- 还有你 - 长官
- And you? - Ma'am.
你不认识我 但我在警校的第一年 你来发表过讲话
You don't know me, but my first year in the Academy, you gave a talk.
你称为「持久游戏」 你谈到道德准则
The "long game" you called it. You talked about a moral compass.
说你相信自己的道德准则永远不会改变
About how you believed in yours immutably.
我当时心想 那个人 总有一天 我要跟他一样
And I thought to myself, "That guy. One day, I want to be that guy."
可现在 一只鸽子？
And now… A pigeon?
严格来说是几只鸽子 但我明白你的意思
Technically, it was a few pigeons, but I hear what you're saying.
好吧 我就这么办
Okay. So here's what I'm going to do.
放你几天假 自己去追鸽子把
You want to take a vacation day? Go on your own? Fine.
但我不会再浪费人力物力陪你捕风捉影了
But I'm not going to devote resources to another snipe hunt.
我是来清理烂摊子 不是来添乱的 非常抱歉
I came to clean this mess up, not add to it. I'm sorry.
头 谢谢 我保证 这绝不是捕风捉影的
Boss, thank you. I promise you, it won't be a snipe hunt.
我们会抓住那些骑士的
We're gonna get those Horsemen.
她人真好
She's great.
问题是 每个人都有两张脸
The problem is when you're two people at the same time,
总有一天会被撕破的
one of them is bound to trip the other.
到了那个时候 我在那儿看着你
And when that happens, I will be there.
牢记在心
Duly noted.
- 噢 嗨 - 你是谁
- Oh. Hi! - Who are you?
- 你在我家干什么 - 说起来挺有趣的
- What are you doing in my… - It's actually a funny story.
你是怎么进来的？哇
How did you get into my apartment? Whoa!
我觉得挺有趣 但其实不是 让人「哈哈」的那种有趣
I think it's funny. It's not like funny "ha ha."
也不是你想象的那种「哈哈」的有趣
Or you might not think that it's funny "ha ha."
我觉得有趣 因为我觉得 这一切都是相关的
I think it's funny. I guess it's all kind of relative.
我其实 不 不是…
I was actually… No, that's not…
我先搬到附近住 现在到了这里 也许…
I made myself in the neighborhood and now I'm here, and maybe…
好吧
Okay.
说真的 你是怎么进来的
Seriously, how did you get in here?
你是疯狂的粉丝吗
Are you some kind of crazed fan or something?
天啊 不 不 不 我认识你
Oh, my God. No, no, no, I recognize you.
你表演了那个二流的极客魔术对吗 你从…
You did that B-grade "geek magic" thing, didn't you? You pulled a…
从兔子里拉出一顶帽子
Pulled a hat out of the rabbit.
从兔子身上拉出帽子 没错
A hat out of the rabbit, that's right.
我知道那样不能成功
I know that it didn't work.
不 那太恶心了
No, it was actually kind of disgusting.
但兔子不介意
It was way worse for the rabbit.
你的破绽明显 道具也很差劲
Well, your drop was obvious and your body shell is flimsy.
所以如果你不介意的话 从我沙发下面爬出来
So if you wouldn't mind crawling out from under my couch and…
嗒嗒 我现在坐在这咯 疯啦
Ta-da! Now I'm sitting over here. Crazy!
顺便说一句 那个兔子戏法？那都是8年前了 好吗
By the way, that rabbit thing? That was eight years ago, okay?
我这几年进步了很多
I've gotten so much better since then.
- 有吗 - 对
- Have you? - Yeah.
好吧 过来 你想要做什么
Okay, come here. What is it that you want?
我想见你 当然人人都想
I wanted to meet you. Everybody, really.
我想成为「天眼」的一员 好吗
I want to be a part of the Eye, okay?
真的 而且我想用我的魔术做好事
I said it. I do. And I want to use my magic for good,
就好像你和梅里特 特别是杰克
like you and Merritt and Jack especially.
没错 我知道那个杰克还活着
Oh, that's right. I know that Jack is alive.
我知道他伪装了自己的死亡
I know that he faked his own death.
我超喜欢假死 太疯狂了
I am a huge fan of faking deaths. That was crazy!
这是什么？车夫结？
What is this? A trucker's hitch?
- 对 - 打的太差劲了
- Yeah. - It's terrible.
- 真丢脸 - 好吧
- Embarrassing. - Okay.
还有 真遗憾亨利离开你了
By the way, I am so sorry that Henley left you.
- 噢 天啊 - 对不起
- Ow! God! - Sorry.
那样其实更好点 知道我听说什么了吗
That's actually a little better. You know what I heard?
- 什么 - 关于亨利？
- What? - About Henley?
我听说 她厌倦了等待
I heard that she got tired of waiting around.
她失去了信仰要求退出
She lost faith and so she asked for an out,
天眼就满足了她
and the Eye gave it to her.
但谁知道呢 对吧
But who knows, right?
内心想法这东西很难说
In matters of the heart, so difficult to tell.
也许她只是厌倦你了 有想过那种可能吗？
I mean, maybe she got sick of you. You ever think about that?
控制欲？
Control issues?
可能你把她绑得不够紧 噢
Maybe you just didn't tie her up tight enough. Ow!
嗯 接下来会这样
Mmm. Here's what's going to happen.
你最好呆在这里 闭上嘴
You're going to stay here and stop talking,
我要打个电话
and I'm going to make a phone call,
在5分钟之内会有人…
and in about five minutes, some people are going…
（新短消息：迪伦）
- 发力都在手腕上 - 嗯哼
- It's all in the wrist. - Uh-huh.
让卡片的冲力替你完成工作
Let the momentum of the card do the work for you.
嗯哼
Mmm-hmm.
最后这一张我叫做「旋转」
This last one I call the Stall.
不错
Not bad.
现在想看个美妙的东西吗
Now you want to see a thing of beauty?
- 想啊 - 走你
- I do indeed. - Here you go.
噼里啪啦砰
And bingo bango bongo.
不 不 挺好的 虽然
That's good. No, no, no, it's good to be positive
这一年半点进步都没有
despite making zero progress in a year.
是啊
Yeah.
但在催眠术方面
Whereas when it comes to hypnotism,
学生几乎就要出师了
the student has almost become the master.
我喜欢你的自信 但你可以说你有更好的老师
I like your confidence, but you might say that you have the better teacher.
- 噢 - 对
- Ooh! - Yeah.
你说得对
You're right. You're right.
你的老师绝对不知道他自己在干什么
Your teacher definitely doesn't know what he's doing.
顺便问一下 这是你昨天的卡牌吗
By the way, was this your card yesterday?
- 没错 - 我想也是
- In fact it was. - I thought so.
还不赖
That's not bad.
如果我能在你用卡牌打中丹尼之前 催眠他
If I can hypnotize Danny before you hit him with a card,
就让我睡一星期上铺
I get top bunk for a week.
成交
Okay, that's a deal.
- 丹尼 最近好嗎？- 嘿
- Danny, what's up, man? - Hey.
盯着你的手掌 随着你的视线移动
Stare at the palm of your hand and as your eyes change focus,
你会开始意识到…
you will begin to notice…
随你怎么说 我没被催眠
Everything, because I'm not hypnotized.
对我不起作用的 求你别变得跟他一样
It's not working. Please don't become him.
我不知道你们在没有女人的时候
I didn't know you guys did party tricks
居然会耍派对上取乐的这些小花招
when there weren't floozies around to impress.
我们在大概1937年的时候就不再
Uh, I think we stopped trying to impress floozies
以让女人动心为目标了
in, like, 1937.
好吧 有人闯进了我的公寓
Okay, somebody broke into my apartment, all right?
那菜鸟了解我的一切
Some amateur who knew everything about me,
了解亨利离开的一切 还有我们的一切
everything about Henley leaving, and everything about us.
- 就是她 - 嘿
- That's her. - Hey!
- 嗨 - 你见过鲁拉了
- Hi. - You met Lula.
见过了 她在这干什么
I've met her. What is she doing here?
我是新骑士 女骑士
I'm the new Horseman! I'm the girl Horseman.
喔
Whoo!
耶
Yeah!
没人激动吗 杰克 不表示下？
Nobody. No excitement. Jack? Anything?
迪伦 告诉我这里是什么情况
Dylan, tell me what's going on here.
鲁拉过去10年都在做幕后工作
Well, Lula's been on the underground scene for the last decade,
我觉得她是有真才实学的
and I think she has some real talent,
我想让她走上台前
and I'd like to try her on stage
- 来平衡一下阳盛阴衰 - 什么？
- to balance out the duo. - What?
你是认真的吗？
No, are you serious, man?
亨利离开后你说过 我可以再回到台上的
After Henley left, you said I could get back on stage again.
现在怎么就凭空冒出来个人
Not someone who just showed up.
我考虑过 真的
I told you I'd think about it, and I have,
但我真的需要你 再跟我一起在幕后多呆一会
and I really need you behind the scenes with me for a little while longer.
迪伦 好了 我这辈子都在幕后啊
Dylan, come on. I've been behind the scenes my whole life.
补充一句 那可是犯罪 你看到那人的脸了吗
Which is a crime, might I add. Have you seen that man's face?
我非常感谢你为团队加入了女性
Much as I appreciate the addition of some femininity to the group,
这已经比阿特拉斯所提供的条件 要好很多了
over and above what Atlas provides,
我觉得我们在这里真正的问题是…
I think the real issue is we've been in this…
真正的问题是我们已经排练几个月了
Yeah, the issue is that we have been rehearsing for months
而我们一无所知
for something… We don't even know what it is.
如果你继续努力直到
And you're going to keep working until…
直到我们融合得像一个人一样 我知道 我听你说过
Until we work as a single organism. I know, I've heard you say that.
问题是 你这么说
The thing is, when you say that,
我觉得你指的是我们 而不包括你
I think what you're referring to is us, not you.
听着 我是直接从天眼那里得到命令的
Listen, I'm getting my orders directly from the Eye.
好吗？然后我把命令转达给你们
Okay? And then I give them to you.
要是你不喜欢 你可以走
Now, if you don't like that, you're welcome to go.
不 我哪都不去 但我 只管自家事
No, I'm not going anywhere. But I'm… Mmm. I'm taking care of myself.
伙计们 我能简短的插一句吗
Guys, can I just weigh in here really quickly?
因为我想我知道这里究竟怎么回事了
Because I think I see what's going on here.
你们是个了不起的 亲如一家的团体
You guys are this amazing, tight-knit family unit.
- 而我是新来的… - 说我们是什么都行 但我们不是家人
- I'm a new person… - We are anything but a family.
好吧 我母亲 有一次还拿刀顶着我爸的脖子
Okay, well, my mother literally knifed my father in the neck one time.
所以其实你们挺像我家人的
So you are actually a little bit like my family unit.
- 真的？- 但是 没错
- Literally? - But, yeah.
我想那是个意外
It was an accident, I think.
好吧 那这意味着我们真的 要做点什么了？
Okay. So, does this mean we're actually going to do something?
对
Yes.
你们都听说过奥克塔和他们的 花花公子CEO 欧文·凯斯
You've all heard of Octa and their playboy CEO, Owen Case.
他的搭档 沃尔特·马布里一年前去世了
His partner, Walter Mabry, died about a year ago.
想不想知道这一切会带来什么？
You wanna know what all this has been leading to?
奥克塔将发布下一代手机
Octa's hosting the launch of the next-gen cell phone.
只要这些手机走上街头
Once these phones hit the streets,
就会把使用者的信息发给黑市
they'll siphon their users' information to the black market.
这意味着奥克塔将出卖用户隐私 来增加自己的利润
Meaning Octa's selling privacy to up their profit.
所以天眼决定揭露他们的阴谋
So, the Eye has decided to expose them for it.
我们的目的就是突袭他们的发布会
Our mission is to hijack the show.
排练结束了 伙计们
Rehearsal's over, guys.
这是我们一直等待的机会
This is what we've been waiting for.
该着重出江湖了
Now it's time to get to work.
（奥克塔）
欢迎 奥克塔开发者
Welcome, Octa insiders,
博客作者 以及记者们
bloggers and journalists.
非常高兴能请到大家 参加我们的特别活动
We're delighted that you've joined us to participate in our special event.
今天标志着社会网络 新旅程的开始
Today marks the beginning of a bright new journey in social networking.
我们的最新产品 奥克塔8代…
Our latest product, Octa 8…
钥匙 手机 平板 放进盒子里
Keys, cell phones, iPads, in the bin.
谢谢 先生
Thank you, sir.
在里面不能发短信 推特 录像 或是吃东西
Can't have you texting, tweeting, recording, or eating.
对不起 我们会替你保管好它的
Sorry, we will take very good care of it for you.
噢 这里有
Oh, by the way.
凯斯先生亲自写的安保备忘录
Security memo from Case himself.
有些客人很奇怪的 要按照他的指示做 是吗？
Couple of surprise guests. Just follow his lead, yeah?
一切都好 我正前往控制室
We're all good. I'm heading to the control room.
好 谢谢 杰克
All right. Thanks, Jack.
- 阿特拉斯 走 - 不 迪伦 我不能…
- Atlas, go. - No, Dylan, I can't…
- 什么？出什么问题了？- 不 人太多了
- What? What's the problem? - No, there's too many people…
阿特拉斯 现在欧文进场了
Atlas, I got Owen landing now.
好的 现在就去
Okay, I'm going now.
- 停下 - 噢
- Stop. - Oh.
- 好了 - 谢谢
- Okay. - Thanks.
帕斯卡 厨房需要你
Pascal, we need you in the kitchen.
听着 演讲的主题是自由好吗
Look, the speech is about freedom, okay?
我们像在这推销的是自由
That's what we're trying to sell here, is freedom.
你到底是哪里搞不懂
Which part of that do you not understand?
- 我的天啊 - 我知道 对不起
- I know, I'm sorry. - For goodness sake!
凯斯先生 呃 我是法律部的约翰
Mr. Case, John from legal.
这需要你的签名才能发布
Just need your signature for release.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
把事情办好然后告诉我
Just get it done and get it back to me.
嘿 伙计 笑一个
Hey there, buddy! Smile!
- 你是谁？搞什么啊 - 我是谁？
- Who are you? What the hell? - Who am I?
今天是照相日 朱莉没跟你说 今天要照相吗
It is picture day. Did Julie not tell you it's picture day?
- 照相日？你说什么啊 - 这是全公司都要执行的
- Picture day? What are you… - Company-wide policy.
- 听着 我还有工作要做 - 我也有工作
- Look, I got a job to do. - I have a job to do, too.
等等 那是什么
Hold on a second. What is that?
我需要一些支援
I'm going to need some backup here.
- 你打电话给谁？- 嘿 那是我的证件
- Who are you calling? - Hey! That's my ID.
保安 我的名字是…
Security, my name is…
- 波·沃尔什 谢谢 - 嘿 我才是波·沃尔什
- Bo Walsh, thank you. - Hey, I'm Bo Walsh!
不是这个人 他不是波·沃尔什
Not this guy. He's not Bo Walsh.
请你冷静点
Calm down, please.
嘿 怎么回事
Hey! Hey, what's going on?
这家伙刚进来拿闪光灯闪我眼睛
This guy just came and put a flashlight in my eyes.
我是在做我的工作 这个人 检查下他的徽章
I'm trying to do my job. This guy, check his badge.
- 这个人是谁？- 我是波·沃尔什 他不是
- Who is this guy? - I'm Bo Walsh, not him.
这里写的是「埃文斯精神病医院」
It says here, "Evans Mental Facility.
- 「D·斯图奇」 - 等等
- Mark D. Stooge." - Hold on a second.
我这辈子都没见过这个
I've never seen this before in my life.
抱歉 沃尔什先生
I'm sorry, Mr. Walsh.
- 来吧 斯图奇先生 - 等等 他不是沃尔什先生
- Come on, Mr. Stooge. - Hold on. He's not Mr. Walsh!
- 来吧 我们走 - 这里怎么回事
- Come on. Let's go. - What's going on here?
我才是波·沃尔什 他不是
I'm Bo Walsh, not him!
天啊 你真的不能再相信这城市的任何人了 对吗
God, you cannot trust anybody in this city anymore, can you?
放开我 我要打电话
Get off me! Look, I want to make a phone call.
- 我要打给我的上司 - 嘿 怎么回事
- I want to call my boss! - Hey, hey! What's going on?
我要打电话给我的上司 这个混蛋…
I want to call my boss, and this jackass…
嘿 去打电话吧 先生 那是你的权力
Hey! Make your phone call. That's your right, sir.
那是我的权力
That's my right.
- 什么鬼 - 你疯了 走
- What the hell? - You're crazy. Let's go.
这不是… 我的手机在哪？
This isn't my… Where's my phone?
我的手机在哪？
Where's my phone?
阿特拉斯 斯图奇离开大楼了
Atlas, Stooge has left the building.
好
Okay.
我们控制电路板了 我要离开后台
The circuit board is ours. I am leaving backstage.
（服务器离线 勿进）
女士们先生们 有请欧文·凯斯
Ladies and gentlemen, Owen Case.
好了 鲁拉 让这些男人们 看看你的本事
All right. Lula, show these guys what you're made of.
这里交给我吧 克拉克说你可以休息了
I can take over from here. Clark says you're on break.
什么休息？克拉克是谁
What break? Who's Clark?
「克拉克是谁」 真有意思
"Who's Clark?" That's funny.
要是我跟罗杰那么说 他会吓坏的
Imagine if I told Roger that, he'd freak out.
- 别那么做 - 什么
- Don't do that! - What?
罗杰又是谁啊
Who the hell is Roger?
莉莎知不知道你不认识罗杰？
Does Lisa know that you don't know Roger?
- 我不知道丽莎是谁 - 你又在开玩笑？
- I don't know who Lisa is. - Are you kidding again?
- 你现在又不认识丽莎了？- 不认识 让开
- You don't know who Lisa is now? - No, I don't. Just get away.
- 那太危险了 - 你把肉都毁了
- That is a dangerous… - You're ruining the meat.
别逼我告诉布莱恩
Don't make me have to go to Brian!
- 我不知道布莱恩是谁 - 你为什么这样
- I don't know who Brian is! - Why are you acting like this?
- 我一会直接告诉他 - 给我
- I'll go straight to him. - Give me…
噢 天啊
Oh, my God!
你对我做了什么
What are you doing to me?
- 救命 - 去帮她
- Help me! - Help her. Go!
喝点水
Have some water.
从你的表情我看出来你被血吓到了
I feel from your face you're freaked by the flow of blood,
但我手指一弹就没事
which is fully fixable in a snap
只要专心和依照我的话做
by focusing and following the flow of my words
仿佛你在流动和飘浮
as you're flowing and floating,
所以你要专注于我的指令
which is why you're focusing on my commands.
你生活中到目前为止的成就
You got this far in life
都是靠听那一个声音 你脑中的声音
by listening to one voice, the voice in your head.
而这就是那个声音
This is that voice.
看着光
Look at the light.
倾听你自己的声音
Listen to your own voice.
天啊
Oh, my God.
喔 那是什么？是魔法毛巾吗
Wow. What is that? Is that a miracle towel?
太感谢了 你知道吗
Thank you so much. Do you know what?
你教会了我 我不适合这种工作
You have taught me that I'm not cut out for this kind of work.
我辞职
Quit!
在拿条毛巾
Get another towel.
谢谢 再见
Thank you, and goodbye.
天啊
Oh, God.
欢迎各位
Welcome everybody!
现在 万众期待的时刻到了
And now, the moment that you've all been waiting for…
- 干得好 女士 - 谢谢
- Nice work, lady. - Thanks.
奥克塔2代的革命性音乐
Revolutionized music with Octa 2.
其实我有点紧张 这都还没上台呢
I'm actually nervous, and I'm not even going onstage.
我听说如果你紧张
You know, I've heard that if you're nervous,
想象对方的裸体会对你有帮助
it can be really helpful to picture each other naked.
其实是想象观众是裸体的
It's actually picture the audience naked.
不 这是新招 新的科学
No, this is new. This is a new science.
我不知道
So, I don't know.
- 你要不要 我们该试试 - 现在没心情
- Do you want… We should try it. - Not the right mood.
看来只能靠我们了 老伙计
Guess that leaves you and me, old buddy.
什么 想象对方… 不 不 谢谢
What? Picture each other… No. No, thank you.
我是说 我承认脖子以上有些问题
I mean, I admit, from the neck up there are issues.
但我的脖子以下 都还是大卫
But from the neck down, the David.
欧文·凯斯
Owen Case.
早上好 奥克塔精英们
Good morning, Octa-lites.
现在 我宣布
Now, I've made the claim…
现在 我宣布过奥克塔8代是绝对的魔法
Now, I've made the claim that Octa 8 is pure magic.
但事实是 那只是那种
But the truth is, that's just one of those things I say…
我说是真相 但其实
You know, the truth is, that's just one of those things I say…
另有含义的东西
…when in fact I mean something else.
但其实是另有含义的东西
那我是指什么？
What else do I mean?
在这里 我将为你们展示 我美妙的谎言和伪善
Well, here to fill you in on some of my fabulous lies and hypocrisy,
并表演一些你们从未见过的 最炫目的魔术
and to perform some of the most dazzling feats of magic you have ever seen…
- 他们是全世界 - 最伟大的魔术师
- They are the world's… - greatest magicians.
来这里揭露我的骗术
Here to expose me for the fraud I truly am.
女士们先生们 有请四骑士
Ladies and gentlemen, here are the Horsemen.
纽约 你好
Hello, New York!
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
嘿 能回来真好
Hey, it's great to be back.
看我们最新的骑士 鲁拉
And have you met our newest Horseman, Lula?
- 感觉很好 对吧 - 感觉太好了
- Feels good, right? - Pretty good. Pretty good.
谢谢 谢谢 好了
Thank you, thank you. Um, okay.
我们想聊聊你们的隐私
We want to talk to you about your privacy.
隐私对你们来说有什么意义？
What does your privacy mean to you?
很明显对欧文·凯斯来说 隐私毫无意义
Because apparently to Owen Case, it means absolutely nothing.
不 其实比没意义还更没意义
No, actually it means less than absolutely nothing.
看 他嘲弄你们的隐私 他蔑视隐私
You see, he's mocked your privacy. He's scorned it.
对 而且我们说的不只是那些
Right, and we're not just talking about the things that you already agreed to
当你看都不看就签下
when you signed, probably without reading
奥克塔客户条款第1-7条的协议
the terms and conditions of Octas 1 through 7.
迪伦 FBI来了
Dylan, the FBI is here.
好 别担心
All right. Don't worry about it.
好 改编成C-4计划
All right, go to plan C-4.
锁门
Lock the doors.
老板 你来了真好
Hey, boss, I'm glad you're here.
别说
Don't.
伙计们 听我说 我们得绕一下 从后面进去
Guys, look. We got to move around, get in through the back.
这些骑士们很狡猾 好吗
These Horsemen are tricky, okay?
他们的后备计划都有后备计划
They got backup plans on top of backup plans.
对不起 不是故意幸灾乐祸的 不过我跟你说过了
Hey, sorry, don't mean to gloat, but I told you so.
别废话了 罗兹
Cut the bullshit, Rhodes.
一小时前我们接到匿名电话
We got an anonymous phone call an hour ago.
那确认了我一直以来跟她说的一切
Confirms everything I've been telling her.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
你派特工去底特律和费城
You sent agents to Detroit and Philadelphia.
一直在喊 狼来了这样我们就不会派他们来这里
You've been crying wolf so we wouldn't send them here.
- 老大 拜托 - 继续开门
- Boss, please. - Keep working on the doors.
求你跟我说 你没信考恩疯狂的幻想
Please tell me that you haven't bought into Cowan's crazy, paranoid fantasia.
在节目开始之前
Before we start the show…
我们让欧文同意了 我们提出的一些条款
We had Owen agree to a few terms and conditions of our own.
所以所有我们曾经认为是隐私的东西…
So, everything that he had once considered private…
他认为是真正隐私的…
That he thinks is really private…
所有他认为是隐私的东西现在…
Yeah, everything that he once considered private is now…
天啊
Oh, my.
就像骑士们喜欢说的 魔术的关键是控制想法
As the Horsemen like to say, magic is about controlling perception.
你们把他们看作真相的勇士 但他们是吗？
You see them as champions of the truth, but are they?
或者说这也是他们营造的幻觉之一？
Or is that just another one of their illusions?
- 怎么回事 罗兹 - 这简直疯了
- What's going on, Rhodes? - This is crazy.
我们得让所有人到另一个入口
We got to get everyone to the other exits.
- 我们走 到后面 - 不 你呆在这
- Let's go, to the back. - No. You stay here.
那么 既然他们这么喜爱秘密
So, since they clearly love secrets…
那就揭露一些他们的秘密好了
Let's reveal some of theirs.
丹尼 各位 离开舞台
Danny, everyone, get off the stage.
撤退
Abort.
杰克 跟他们一起走 我会在集合点跟你们碰面
Jack, go with them. I'll see you at the meet-up point.
快走
Let's go.
记不记得杰克·怀尔德之死？
Do you recall the death of Jack Wilder?
如果我跟你们说他其实没死 而且就在这儿会怎么样？
What if I told you he's not just alive, but he's actually right here.
知道还有谁在这吗 FBI
And do you know who else is here? The FBI.
让他们进来吧 好吗
Let's let them in, shall we?
现在 惊天秘密
And now, for the big reveal.
走 上舞台
Go! Go! To the stage.
有第五个骑士
There's a fifth Horseman,
而他是他们之中最大的罪犯
and he's the biggest criminal of them all.
FBI特工 迪伦·罗兹
FBI agent, Dylan Rhodes.
- 我就知道 - 什么？
- I knew it. - What?
这水要比你知道深得多 老大
This is so much deeper than you know, boss.
你以为自己看着一样东西 但你根本不懂
You think you're looking at one thing, but you have no idea.
- 你是谁 - 跟我一直以来一样
- Who are you? - The same man I've always been.
伙计们 对不起
Boys, I'm sorry.
这是在耍我吧
You gotta be kidding me.
- 我们要去滑管 - 快走
- We've gotta get to the chute. - Go!
- 这些人是谁 - 管谁呢 快走
- Who are those guys? - Who cares? Come on!
- 快 快 - 继续走
- Hurry, hurry! - Keep going!
这是怎么发生的
How the hell could this happen?
我以为一切都在迪伦的掌控之中
I thought Dylan had everything under control.
对 很明显他没掌控
Yeah. Apparently he didn't.
也许是你泄露的 丹 你鬼鬼祟祟的干嘛去了？
Maybe you're the leak, Dan. Where you been sneaking off to?
你居然敢暗示我…
Don't you dare for a second insinuate that I had…
- 我没在暗示 那是你 - 我们上车 快点
- I'm not insinuating. That's your… - Let's get to the truck, come on!
- 一起走 - 走 走
- Stay together! - Move! Move!
鲁拉 快点
Lula, come on!
来了 喔
Coming! Whoa!
喔 喔 喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
睡 睡 睡 睡
Sleep. Sleep. Sleep. Sleep.
怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
- 怎么不是车子？- 我们在哪？
- Wasn't there supposed to be a truck? - Where the hell are we?
走
Come on!
嘿 嘿 你接错管子了吗？
Hey, hey! Wait, did you mis-run the tube?
没 我接到车子里了 我知道我接好了
No, I put it in the truck. I know I did!
因为我们现在真的不是在车上
Because we're really not in the truck right now.
一定有人移动管子
Somebody must have moved the tube.
我们在一间中国餐厅上方？
Were we above a Chinese restaurant? Give me that!
- 我在走 轻点 - 有地方出问题了
- I'm moving! Relax! - There's something very wrong.
好吧 我们为什么在这？
Okay. Why are we here?
我为什么这么饿
Why am I frickin' starving?
对 我也很饿
Yeah, I'm weirdly starving, too.
这没道理啊
This makes no sense.
好了 对不起
Okay, sorry.
至少 我知道虽然这没法安慰人
At least, and I know this isn't much consolation,
不过很明显现在我们被 中国菜包围了
but apparently we're now surrounded by Chinese food.
- 对吧？- 伙计们
- Right? - Guys…
我觉得我们现在这地方 不能光用「中国菜」来形容
I think where we are right now, they don't refer to it as "Chinese food."
这就叫做「菜」
It's just called "food."
等等 你说什么？这怎么可能？
Wait, what are you saying? How is this possible?
我相信用你独特的说法 那个词应该是「魔术」
I believe in your particular parlance, the word is "magic."
那家伙跟你长得一样
That guy looks exactly like you.
跟你长得一模一样 你看到了吗
He looks exactly like you. Are you seeing this right now?
沙斯
Chase.
你这表情让我觉得就像听 别人说自己见到滚石乐队
Must confess, it's like what I heard about meeting the Rolling Stones.
发现他们真人比相片矮一点
They're a lot shorter in person.
记不记得我跟你们说过有一个 我做什么他都捣乱的人？
Remember I told you about the guy who screwed me out of everything?
这就是我的双胞胎兄弟 沙斯
This is my twin brother, Chase.
等等 这是你干的？
Wait, did you do this?
如你们所见 我的老板不喜欢乱来
As you can see, my boss don't mess around.
我完全不明白现在这是怎么回事
I do not understand what is going on right now. At all.
好吧 让我替你们说明一下
Okay, let me break it down for you.
你们从纽约的一个屋顶跳下来 落到了澳门
You jumped off a rooftop in New York and you landed in Macau.
也叫中国的维加斯
AKA the Vegas of China.
快速转移
And presto-changeo.
你不喜欢吗
Don't you just love it?
「全世界最伟大的魔术师们」
The "greatest magicians in the world"
居然成了别人魔术里面的道具
are the object of someone else's magic trick?
这难道不是很诗意吗
Isn't that poetic?
不觉得？知道吗 我不会让你们倒我胃口的
No? You know what, I'm not gonna let you guys yuck my yum.
咻咻 还是姆咻 走吧
Shoo-shoo. Or mu-shu. Whatever.
噢 还有知不知道他们说的「发生在澳门的」
Oh, and you know what they say, "What happens in Macau…"
下半句不记得了 因为是用中文说的
Uh, well, I don't know the rest of it, 'cause it's in Chinese, uh…
谢谢 伙计们
Hey, thanks, guys!
据报称臭名昭著的四骑士
Reports are coming in that the infamous Horsemen
操控了今天的奥克塔新品发布会
hijacked the Octa product launch today.
但他们反而被摆了一道
The trick was on them, however,
我们也知道了杰克·怀尔德 奇迹般的复活
as we learned of the miraculous resurrection of Jack Wilder.
以及FBI特工迪伦·罗兹其实是
And the stunning revelation that FBI Agent Dylan Rhodes
部门里内鬼这一惊人事实
has been working as a mole within the Bureau.
如今疑云密布 如今全球范围内已经展开
Questions abound today as an international manhunt is underway
迪伦·罗兹 以及他及其神出鬼没的魔术师犯罪集团
for Dylan Rhodes and his elusive and criminal band of illusionists.
嘿 真的 你们在哪？
Hey, seriously, where are you guys?
我在接头点 还给你们留了言
I'm at the meetup. I've been leaving you messages.
但一点消息都没有 求你们打我电话
I haven't heard from anyone. Please, call me!
周四股市
And the stock market
在大涨后小回
saw big gains and modest losses on Thursday.
（未知来电）
嘿 告诉我你很安全 你在哪
Hey, tell me you're safe. Where are you?
就在你18个月前丢下我的地方 罗兹特工
Right where you left me, 18 months ago, Agent Rhodes.
塔迪乌斯？
Thaddeus?
失去一切的感觉如何？
How does it feel to lose everything?
你的工作 你的身份 你活下去的理由
Your job. Your identity. Your reason for living.
失去掌控的滋味如何？也许这是你第一次尝到？
How does it feel to be out of control, perhaps for the first time?
你为谁工作
What do you want?
你是个蠢货 罗兹特工 一直都是
You're a fool, Agent Rhodes. You always have been.
- 他们在哪？- 我不会在电话里告诉你
- Where are they? - I'm not telling you on the phone!
他们在哪里？
Where are they?
如果你想知道 四骑士最近遭遇的挫折 背后是不是我指使的
And if you're wondering if I was behind the Horsemen's recent debacle,
这就交给你自己去调查了
I'll let you work that out for yourself.
嘿 我烧死过你一次 我还会再烧一次的
Hey, I burned you once, I'll burn you again.
我不在玩游戏 塔迪乌斯
I'm not playing, Thaddeus.
这不是我的游戏 罗兹特工 是你的
It's not my game, Agent Rhodes. It's yours.
当你把我锁进牢房时 你就开始了游戏
You started it when you locked me in a cell.
这一局只是轮到我走而已
This is simply my move.
下一步该你了
Next one is yours.
不
No!
放开
Let go!
爸爸 救命 爸爸
Dad! Help me! Dad!
爸爸
Dad!
关键在于盲点
It's all about blind spots.
当你直接盯着一样东西 却看不到它 为什么？
When you're staring straight at something, and not see it. Why?
盲点
Blind spots.
这是我们一起学到的 不是吗兄弟
We learned that together, didn't we, bro?
他有没有跟你们说过 我们曾经是搭档？
Did he tell you that we were partners once?
没有？不会没说过吧 著名的「小麦金尼兄弟」
No? I didn't think so. The "Mini-McKinneys."
切西和梅比
Chasey and a Mer-Bear
会让你吓死
Gonna make you scare-bear
魔法麦金尼
Ma-ma-magic McKinneys
酷
Cool.
然后一天 我们12岁 弗吉尼亚·冯·威尔谢姆
And then, one day, we were 12 and Virginia von Welsheim
在街头举行了一个很棒的派对
had a very nice party down the street.
我有点情况不能去
I had a little tum-tum, couldn't go.
梅比自己去了 尝到了独自表演的甜头
Mer-Bear did it on his own, and got a taste of the solo thing, and uh…
- 然后就把我一脚踢开 - 天啊
- …and kicked me to the curb. - Oh, God.
沙斯 你赢了 我承认 你是怎么做的
Chase, you win! I concede. Just tell me how you did it.
快递员 一个月前来到你家 小萨？
Delivery guy came to your door about a month ago, little za.
萨？
Za?
披萨
Pizza, huh?
- 这是D3375公寓吗 - 完全不是
- Is this apartment D3375? - Not even close.
（睡吧）
睡吧
Sleep!
放松 漂浮 飘荡 入梦
Relaxing, floating, drifting, dreaming…
坠落
Falling.
所以 我的小兄弟
So, what he did, my little womb-mate,
下载了你所有的私人信息
is he downloaded all your private information,
我的老板有了他需要的一切
and my employer had all he needed.
谢谢
Thanks.
你怎么知道怎么找他
How did you know how to find him?
- 真是个好问题 阿特拉斯 - 好吧
- That's a very good question, Atlas. - Okay.
跟着警卫 他们会带你去见我的老板
Just follow the guards. They'll take you to my boss.
跟你玩猫捉老鼠很有意思 兄弟
Been fun playing this cat-and-mouse with you, broski.
喵
Meow.
玩的开心
Have fun at the Sands.
- 真是非常 非常对不起 - 对 你应当道歉
- I am so, so, so sorry. - Yeah, you should be.
别再说我背叛我们了 好吗
Don't ever accuse me of betraying us again, okay?
你们有没有想过天眼正在看着这一切
Do you guys ever think that the Eye is watching this?
也许这就是他们想要的？
You know, that maybe this is even what they want?
在某个瞬间
And at the exact right moment,
他们会突然出现 然后我们会…
they're gonna swoop in, and we'll be like,
「太好了 谢天谢地你来了」
"Yes! Thank God you're here!
「谢天谢地 来的刚刚好 天眼」
Thank God! Just in the nick of time, Eye!"
然后我们会庆祝 到最后一切都是值得的？
And then we'll just celebrate, and it was all worth it in the end?
其实我也不是那么想的 所以…
I don't even really think that, either, so…
没事
It's cool.
啊
Ah.
嗒嗒
Ta-da!
跟你们合作我太开心了
So happy to be working with you.
请进 请进
Please, come in. Come in.
喔 喔 喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
对不起 你是怎么跟我们合作的
Wait, sorry, how are you working with us?
就跟魔术师从帽子里拽出兔子一样
Oh, well, as much as a magician who pulls a rabbit from a hat
要跟那兔子合作
is working with that rabbit.
我们会合作的 没错 我想介绍一下自己…
We'll be working together. Yes. Allow me to introduce myself.
对 你是沃尔特·马布里 你一年前死了
Yeah, you're Walter Mabry. You died a year ago.
对 我这点子是学你的 怀尔德先生
Yes. An idea I got from you, Mr. Wilder.
伪装自己的死 然后世界就会放下防备
Fake your death, the world puts its guard down.
我控制了那么几家公司
I'm able to control quite a few companies,
包括我老搭档欧文的
including my old partner, Owen's,
用的是所谓的匿名持股者组成的财团
as a consortium of so-called anonymous shareholders.
- 那违反了多少条证监会法律？- 应该是每一条都违反了
- And that violates how many SEC laws? - I believe it breaks all of them.
每一条
All of them.
你看 你们都想要观众
You see, you all want an audience.
迫切的需要一个观众 这真的很让人难过
Need one, desperately. It's quite sad, really.
只是 我虽然有能力抓住你们
Hence, my ability to nab you.
但另一方面 我想要的正好完全相反
I, on the other hand, want the opposite of that.
我只想 而且现在正是百分百的在体制之外
I just want to be, and I am 100 percent off the grid.
知道为什么吗？
You know why?
知道 因为体制是为真正的人准备的
Yeah, because the grid is for actual human beings.
不 因为在一个大数据的世界
No, because in a world of total surveillance,
唯一真正的自由只存在于不被看见之中
the only true freedom lies in not being seen.
你不能从体制内控制体制
You can't control the grid from within the grid.
- 跟我来 - 好吧
- Follow me. - Yeah.
- 跟我来 - 好了好了
- Follow me. - Okay. All right.
你从兔子身上拽出了一顶帽子 那真是让人眼前一亮
You pulled a hat out of a rabbit. That was very colorful.
那是大概8年半之前了 所以 不用特意提起
Almost eight and a half years ago. So, no need to bring that up.
毕竟我们不能为青春时期犯下的 所有错误都买单
We can't all be held accountable for our adolescent personas.
对吧 大魔术师？
Can we, Magicolio?
那都是15年前了
Magicolio, that was 15 years ago.
别误会了 我喜欢那个
Don't get me wrong, I love magic.
我跟你和很多其他人
Like you, and many others who,
一样高中没有过性经历 虽然尝试过
I suppose, were not getting any sex in high school, I dabbled with it.
但不像你们 我能够力求转变追求真正的魔术
But, uh, unlike you, I was able to transition upward towards actual magic.
科学 你们可能都听说过
Science, you may have heard it called.
那么 朋友们 想不想知道 我是怎么把你们弄到这的？
So, would you like to know, my friends, just how I got you here?
我们知道你是怎么做的
We know how you did it.
你不知道
No, you don't.
对 你偷了我们节目的文件 然后很明显把我们催眠了
Yeah, you stole our files for the show, then obviously hypnotized us.
真的 别说了
Stop. No. Seriously, stop.
管道里有连续的声音
The strobe was a combo of binaural beats, as well as…
我说了住嘴
I said stop!
你们可能不觉得有趣 但我觉得
You might not be having fun, but I am.
你这表现方式真独特
You have an unusual way of showing it.
那么
So…
我是怎么做到的
How did I do it?
简单 你看魔术师喜欢 控制别人的视角
Easy. You see, magicians like to control other people's perceptions.
你们在激动紧张之中
In your heightened state of agitation,
看到了最简单的方法 楼顶 黑色管道
you saw the simplest cues. Black tube, roof.
你一心想着跳下去
And your minds filled in the rest.
但你们原本应该跳进去的那根管子 就在你们右侧20英尺
But the tube you meant to go down was 20 feet to your right.
来吧 坐下 坐下 不用一直站着
Go on, sit down. There's no one standing in your way.
我不介意站着
Don't mind if I do.
总之 你们进入管道之后 没错 你说得对
Anyway, once in the tube, yes, you're right…
巴拉巴拉 管道里含有螺旋形灯管以及词语「睡吧」
Blah, blah, blah, the strobe contained UV letters pulsing the word "sleep".
灯光加上声音让你们 很快进入了催眠模式
And that, combined with the sound, put you into an instant alpha pattern.
睡吧 睡吧
Sleep, sleep, sleep.
在那之后才是真正有趣的部分
And from then on, it really was just fun.
我可以向你们保证 你们不知道发生了什么
And I can assure you, you don't know what happened.
（我们的澳门之旅）
真吓人 非常非常吓人
That's really creepy. Really, really creepy.
那不酷
That's not cool.
对 很简单 魔术
Yep, easy stuff, magic,
只要你用心
if you put your mind to it.
好了 够了 那为什么带我们来这
All right, that's enough. So why are we here, then?
除了让我们看到你有多聪明
Besides you getting to show off how adorably clever you are.
就从去年你们盗窃的那个人开始吧
Well, to start with, the man you stole from last year,
我发现我在 他的一些公司里投了不少钱
turns out I had invested quite a lot of money in some of his companies,
所以你们偷的钱中很大一部分 其实是我的
so a lot of what you stole was, in fact, mine.
好消息是 你们回报我的方式很简单
Good news is, it's very easy for you to pay me back.
我只需要你们的技术
I just need your skills.
欧文和我就像甲壳虫乐队 如果甲壳虫曾经是…
Owen and I were like the Beatles, if the Beatles had been…
艾尔芬？
Elfin?
天才
…geniuses.
甲壳虫乐队当然是天才
Pretty sure the Beatles were geniuses.
就像他们一样 我们有过梦想
And like them, we had a dream.
我们能不能创造真正的 原声的魔法？
Could we create actual, genuine magic?
我想你们之中有一人实现了 那个梦想 而那不是你？
And I'm guessing one of you achieved that dream, and it wasn't you?
那只是他希望你这么想
That is what he would like you to think.
我的梦想是优雅和技术的完美结合
My vision was a perfect blend of elegance and technology.
但欧文希望独吞成果 所以他羞辱我
But Owen wanted it for himself so he humiliated me
把我的私人文件透露给了董事会
by exposing my private files to the board of directors
说服了他们相信我不稳定
and convinced them that I am unstable.
他睡着的时候你有没有给他拍照？
Did you take a picture of him while he was sleeping?
他把我踢出了我自己的公司
He had me kicked out of my own company,
然后独占了一块芯片的设计
and now he goes around taking credit for a chip
那不只是一台计算机的关键
that's not just the key to one computer,
而且能控制地球上所有的计算机系统
but every computer system on the planet.
它能解码一切 破解防火墙
It can un-encrypt anything, crack the defense firewall,
操纵市场 监控任何人
manipulate markets, and spy on anyone.
现在它已经被卖给出价更高的买家了
And now it's being sold to the highest bidder.
如果你这么有钱为什么不直接去买
If you're so rich, why don't you just buy it?
然后让他得到钱？
So he gets the money?
还有成功的快乐？不行
And the pleasure? No.
况且如果能让你们为我偷过来 为什么还要去买呢
No, no, no. Besides, why would I buy it when I could have you steal it for me?
它将在明天被展示给一些意向买家
It's being previewed tomorrow to the various suitors,
其中包括你们的目标 一个南非黑帮带领的团队
which will include your targets, a crew lead by a South African gangster.
南非黑帮吗
South African gangster.
对 怎么绕过安保是你们的问题
Yes. How your team gets past security, that's up to you.
但只要进去了你们只要 查看并偷走芯片
But once you do, you just need to inspect it and steal it.
就这样？
That's it?
来吧 这最适合你们了不是吗
Come on, this is perfect for you, isn't it?
你们是魔术师和窃贼
You're magicians and thieves.
你为什么会认为我们会 考虑这件工作？
What makes you think we would even consider doing this?
等等 我有个理由 是什么来着？噢 对了
Um, oh, wait, I had a reason. What was it? Oh, yes.
你看 在老家你们是通缉犯
You see, back home, you're wanted criminals.
但在这里我控制警察 赌场 媒体
But here, I control the police, the casinos, the media.
我可以给你们全新的生活 不再躲躲藏藏
I can give you a new life, out of hiding.
如果你们不接受 我会杀了你吗
And if you don't, I'll have you killed.
你知道吗 我不会为你偷任何东西
You know what? I'm not stealing a thing for you.
- 除非迪伦告诉我可以干 - 真的？那迪伦到底在哪呢？
- Not unless Dylan tells me it's okay. - Really? Dylan is where, exactly?
对 我同意他说的 所以你可以杀了我们
It doesn't matter. Yeah, I'm with him. So you can go ahead and kill us
因为我也不会为你偷任何东西
because I'm not gonna steal anything for you either.
看来我们达成一致了 沃尔特
Strikes me that a consensus seems to be forming, Walter,
我们认为你在虚张声势
and we're calling your bluff.
- 实际上 我们干 - 什么
- Actually, we'll do it. - What?
我们在澳门 全世界最古老的 魔术商店就在这里
We're in Macau. The oldest magic store in the world is here.
我们能拿到需要的东西 然后就干
We'll get the supplies we need, and we'll do it.
谢谢
Thank you.
应该会很有趣的
It should be fun.
沙斯早上 会带你们去商店
Chase will take you to the magic shop in the morning.
（纽堡联邦监狱 联邦惩教所）
警徽
Badge.
真的？
Really?
谢谢
Thanks.
考恩特工 你的证件
Agent Cowan. Your ID.
噢对 谢谢
Oh, yeah. Thanks.
看来布拉德利先生还在吃晚饭
It appears Mr. Bradley's still at dinner.
是吗？跟他说休息结束了
Yeah? Tell him recess is over.
什么？
What?
（囚犯宣称遭陷害）
（我是受害者 撒迪厄斯·布兰德利）
好吧 这一步我走了
All right, so I made my move.
他们在哪 我没时间废话
Where are they? I don't have time for bullshit.
多亏了你我有的是时间
Oh, I have all the time in the world, thanks to you.
我还没吃完我的龙虾 这让我很不爽
And I didn't get to finish my lobster, which makes me very grumpy.
好吧别废话了 你想要什么
Okay, let's cut the crap. What do you want?
可以先从别装得这么强硬开始
You can dispense with the tough guy act to begin with.
你太想装得像了
You're too desperate for it to be believable.
我说了 你想要什么
I said, what do you want?
你用了搜查令里的219表格 来搜查我的房间
You used a form 219 warrant to search my room.
找到了我和四骑士之间的联系
You found a connection between me and the Four Horsemen.
这意味着 你可以带我离开这里24小时
Which means you can take me out of here on a 24-hour leave.
- 你要我帮你越狱？- 我要你带我出去
- You want me to break you out? - I want you to take me out.
你要的就是引渡令
All you need is an extradition order,
你可以在我的印刷机上找到
which you'll find in that tray by my printer.
迪伦 我和四骑士的消失 没有任何关系
Dylan, I had nothing to do with the Horsemen's disappearance.
你被引诱进入一个陷阱
You were lured into a trap.
就像桃乐西到达奥兹国时那样
And like Dorothy did when she landed in Oz,
你开始意识到 离开的唯一方式 就是传过去
you're beginning to realize that the only way out is through.
而只有我可以帮你过去
And I'm the only one who can get you there.
你装了窃听器
You got this place wired.
不需要我帮忙你都可以离开 这都是为了偿还
You don't need me to get out of here. This is all about payback.
- 我相信以眼还眼 - 所以你是要出去毁掉我？
- I believe in an eye for an eye. - So you're out to destroy me?
当然了
Oh, absolutely.
你为我还会玩你的小游戏吗
You think I'm still gonna play your little game?
我知道你会的
I know you will.
因为不管你多努力的尝试 这一切幕后的罪犯
Because no matter how hard you try to find a culprit behind all this,
你都只会怪罪自己
you're going to blame only yourself.
在18个月前将我投进监狱 结束了你的小小复仇之后
When your little vendetta ended with you putting me in jail 18 months ago,
你累了 放松了 你不再注意
you got tired, you got sloppy. You stopped paying attention.
那就是你失败的地方
And that's where you lost.
那么 你可以救你自己
So, you can save yourself,
或者跟我做个交易 救出四骑士
or you can make a deal with me, and save the Four Horsemen,
别再浪费我们俩的时间
and stop wasting both of our time.
为这个自恋狂小个子偷一样东西？我不喜欢
Steal something for this narcissistic little man boy? I don't like it.
但我更不喜欢你替我们做决定
But what I like less is you deciding for us.
是吗？那你喜欢让我们沦为 魔术界的笑柄
Yeah? Do you like that we're the laughing stocks of the magic world,
以及现实世界的难民？
and the fugitives of the actual world?
沃尔特说得对 我们无处可去
Walter is right. We have nowhere to go.
但我们可以改变这点
But we can fix that.
- 你可以改变这？- 对
- We can fix it? - Yeah.
那你现在正式成为团队成员了？
So you're officially part of the team now?
- 你说什么？- 迪伦说我们应该像
- Excuse me? - I'm sure this is what Dylan
一个有机体一样肯定就是这个意思
meant when he said we should all work as a single organism.
对 那就是迪伦告诉他自己 还有我们的童话故事
Yeah, that is a fairytale that Dylan tells himself, and tells us.
听着 就算我们拿到那东西 他也绝不会放我们走
Look, even if we get this stick, he'll never let us go.
我们不能相信沃尔特 好吗 天眼在澳门有过一段历史
We can't trust Walter, okay? The Eye has a history in Macau.
我们只能相信他们
They're the only ones we can trust.
如果能联系上他们
Now, if we can get it to them,
他们就能洗刷我们的名誉 然后让我们离开这
they can clear our names and get us the hell out of here.
这是个馊主意 伙计
It's a bad plan, man.
嘿
Hey.
嗨 你好吗
Hi, how are you?
我们需要一些定制的东西
Um, we need some things custom-made.
实际上明天就要 我们有点赶时间
Actually, by tomorrow. We're kind of in a rush.
然后…
And…
你不知道我在说什么对吗
You have no idea what I'm talking about, do you?
好了
好 不要吵 来了
欢迎来到翁氏商店 我叫李 不是李小龙
Welcome to long's. My name's Li. Not Bruce Lee.
- 什么 - 吓到你了
- What? - Got you.
- 好吧 - 看
- Okay. - Look.
跑去哪了？
Where'd it go?
噢 现在在我头上了 真有意思
Oh! And now it's by my head. How fun.
- 20美元 - 20美元？
- $20. - $20?
不了 谢谢 我们有点赶时间
No, thank you. We're kind of in a rush.
- 10美元 - 呃 不要
- $10. - Uh, no.
- 买1送1 - 不要
- Two for one. - No.
好吧 给我们大拇指就行
Okay, all right. Just give us the thumbs. Yeah?
好 多谢 杰克 请拿着这个
Okay. Thanks a lot, Jack. Please take these.
我们需要藏牌器
So, we need a Keplinger holdout,
还需要止滑剂 隐形指腹 假袖 轨道
and we also need roughing fluid, a Sanada gimmick, sleeves, tracks.
不过都要塑料的 如果可以的话
This is all in plastic, though, if you can.
这位先生说他要塑料的 所有道具
塑料道具
塑料
什么
What?
他谁啊 这也太差了
有问题吗
Is there a problem?
我奶奶想知道为什么是塑料的 塑料的都是便宜货
My grandmother wants to know why plastic? Plastic is cheap.
对不起 我们需要塑料的因为…
Sorry. Yeah, we need plastic because we're…
我们要通过非常敏感的金属探测器
We're going through a very sensitive metal detector, okay?
所以 塑料 没事 金属…
So plastic, nothing. Metal…
能探测到
It detects.
傻瓜 就算你
我还是听不懂
她说什么？
What did she say?
她说就算你说得很慢 还手脚比划
She said just because you're talking slowly and moving your hands
她也不能突然就听得懂英语
doesn't mean she can suddenly understand English.
噢 对 真对不起 他是种族主义者
Oh, yeah. So sorry. He's racist.
听着 我知道唯一我们有共识的
Hey, bro. Listen, I know that the only thing that we agree on
就是我们的父母生的孩子太多了
is that our mom and dad had one too many children.
所以为什么不让就孩子们玩他们的玩具
So why don't we just let the kids play with their toys
我们去喝一杯？
and go get a little drinkey-poo?
- 如果免费的话 没问题 - 太好了 伙计们 我们马上回来
- If it's free, it's me. - Great. Guys, we'll be right back.
好了 孩子们 监护人在看着你们
Okay, kiddies, the chaperones are watching you.
别做会让我不高兴的事
Don't do anything I wouldn't enjoy.
好 你们俩玩的开心
Okay. Have fun, you two.
嘿 能借电话用吗？有件事挺重要的
Hey. Can I use your phone? It's kind of important.
没问题
Sure.
- 免费的 - 谢谢
- On the house. - Thanks.
你打电话给谁
Who are you calling?
我要安排转移芯片
I'm arranging to hand over the stick.
我们就是这么联系天眼的？
So that's how we've been contacting the Eye?
你一直自己联系？
You've been doing it on your own?
也许
Maybe.
天啊 迪伦不会喜欢这样的
Oh, God. Dylan's not gonna like this.
我不是很关心迪伦喜欢怎么样 好吧
I'm not really concerned with what Dylan likes. Okay?
我这是为了我们
I'm doing this for us.
- 这东西怎么回事 - 嘿 轻点 这只是孩子的玩具
- What is wrong with this thing? - Hey, relax, it's just a kid's toy.
对 我也是这么想的
Yeah, that's what I thought.
- 好 让我来 - 噢
- Okay. Let me just… - Ow!
对不起 天啊
Sorry, sorry. Jesus.
嘿 能开这个吗
Hey, can you get this?
简直就像重生
It's like birth, you know.
一个人进入医院 两个人出来
One person enters the hospital, two people come out.
边走边说
Walk and talk.
我会在飞机上告诉你
I'll tell you on the plane.
什么飞机
What plane?
我的线人告诉我你的骑士们在澳门
My sources tell me your Horsemen are in Macau.
- 这表情怎么回事 - 不关你的事
- What's the look? - It's none of your business.
你的线人是谁
Who are your sources?
就是些老朋友
Just some old friends.
等拿到卡我去哪
When we have the card, where do I go?
0比52
And O for 52.
完美 完美的比分
Well, it's perfect. It's a perfect score.
那女孩们呢？
Then what about girls?
感情史？
Like, relationships?
什么？
What?
听着 这不是我引以为傲的故事
Look, it's not something I'm proud of,
但每个我亲近的女孩 最后我都辜负了她们的信任
but every girl I get close to, I end up taking their trust.
还掏空了她们的钱包
And then their wallet.
所以…
So…
- 你拿她们的钱包？- 对
- You take their wallets? - Yeah.
还拿她们的皮带吗？
You ever take their belts?
或者 酒店吧台的花生？
Or how about some peanuts from the hotel bar?
不知道你拿那些干什么
Not sure why you took those.
对不起 你是不是以为我也跟 其他女孩一样？
I'm sorry, did you think that I was like those other girls?
噢 杰克
Oh, Jack.
好 街尾有个市场
Okay. So there's a marketplace down the street.
我要见一个戴蓝帽子的人
And I'm meeting a man with a blue hat.
他会找到合适的人带我们回家
He'll get the stick to the right people and get us home.
你去叫上梅里特好吗？我们有很多事要做
You go grab Merritt, okay? We got a lot to do.
还有 嘿 系上腰带
And, hey, put your belt on.
噢 不是那样的 她从我身上解下来的…
Oh, no, it's not… She took it off me and…
你知道 我这辈子最伤心的时刻
You know, the most heartbreaking moment of my life
就是当我发现 你偷走了我所有的钱然后分了
was when I discovered that you had stolen all my money and split.
我知道现在才发现
I didn't realize until now
你当时拿了多大一笔钱
how much of that money you put into your face.
说真的 鼻子下面的毛 比头顶的还多不觉得奇怪吗
Seriously, is it weird to have more hair in your nose than on your head?
说起来 下次你植发的时候
Speaking of, next time you get a hair transplant,
你应该考虑下别的产品 而不是老头子的鸟毛
you might wanna consider requesting something other than old man pubes.
你真是个小丑 小梅
You know what? You are such a buffoon, Mer-Bear.
你自己拖住我 让你朋友
And this little ploy you have
在背后搞我老板的这套小把戏
of stalling me while your friends screw over my employer?
是行不通的
Not gonna work.
沙斯 当你直视我的双眼 你会发现自己想睡觉
Chase! As you stare into my eyes, you will find that you wanna sleep.
当你醒来 你会祈求梅里特的原谅
When you wake, you will beg for Merritt's forgiveness
并弄明白自己永远比不上他的一半好
and realize that you will never be half the man that he is.
梅里特 真的非常非常对不起
Merritt, I am so, so very, very sorry
你的这个学生真是太可悲了
about how pathetic your pupil is.
嘿 给你一个关于惊喜的建议
Hey, a little hint on your technique of surprise.
你的惊喜根本就没有一点 惊喜所需要的元素
It lacks that all-essential little element of surprise.
嘿 这很有意思 小梅 下次有空再试试
Hey, this has been fun, Mer-Bear. Let's do it again sometime.
好吧 我有足够的时间做一些研究
Well, I've had ample time to do some research, and you know,
我似乎错了
I was wrong.
我认为 天眼也许是真的
I think the Eye might actually be real.
我还以为你不信那些
Thought you didn't buy into all that.
要是我说我不认为
I'd be lying if I said I didn't think
这条路能指引我找到幕后的 伟大魔术师
that this road would lead to the great wizard behind the curtain
并最终见到他的脸 那我肯定在撒谎
and, in the end, I might get to see his face.
那是不可能的
That ain't gonna happen.
即使四骑士的性命都寄托于此？
Even if the fate of the Horsemen depends on it?
听我说 我把你带出来了 我们现在不会改变协议
Listen to me. I broke you out of there. We're not changing the terms now.
- 是你把我弄进去的 - 对 因为你活该呆在那
- You put me there! - Yeah, because you deserve to be there.
- 听着 我没杀你父亲 - 什么
- Listen, I did not kill your father. - What?
好吧 好吧 就别废话了
All right, all right, let's just cut the bullshit.
我知道你是谁 施莱克
I know who you are, Shrike.
我知道你把你爸爸的死怪在我身上
I know you blame me for your father's death.
我知道你认为
I know you think
是我刺激他 让他冲动尝试危险戏法
I goaded him into performing a trick he couldn't pull off.
我知道进监狱是30年报复计划的结果
I know the time in jail was a result of a 30-year revenge plot against me.
就算那些都是针对 你觉得我会现在告诉你吗
Supposing that's all true, you think I'd tell you now?
天啊
Man…
30年
Thirty years.
创造了史上最伟大的长时间魔术技法
Thirty years, and the greatest long game magic trick ever created.
就为了把我关进监狱 好吧
Just to put me behind bars. Okay.
看到我进去感觉如何？
So how did it feel, seeing me there?
那一切就是你所希望的吗
Was it all you hoped?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
你在撒谎 那是空虚的感觉
You're lying. It was an empty experience.
想知道我怎么知道的吗
And you wanna know how I know?
我知道因为你知道
I know because you know.
永远 永远都是 不只是表面的这些
There's always, always more than what's on the surface.
那又怎么样 过去的事情没有发生 你也不是我想象的那样？
So what, the past didn't happen, and you're not who I think you are?
别跟我说30年里
Now, don't tell me in 3O years
这是你第一次问自己那个问题
that's the first time you've asked yourself that question.
我不是我爸爸 你没法影响我 好吗
I am not my father. You're not getting in my head, okay?
你以为能把我引入陷阱？你不行
You think you're luring me into a trap? You're not.
现在我是很急 这意味着我很危险
Now, I am desperate, which means I'm dangerous.
我唯一担心的就是四骑士的安全
My only concern is the health and well-being of the Horsemen.
你要带我找到他们 如果你不带 我保证
And you're gonna lead me to them. And if you don't, I promise you,
你的下场绝对比 轻松的躺在牢房里要悲惨的多
you're gonna end up far worse than in some cushy jail cell somewhere.
要是四骑士其实不需要你拯救呢？
What if the Horsemen don't actually need you to save them?
好 实验室是由两个分离的隔断组成
All right. So the lab is made up of two distinct layers,
安保外围以及无菌室
the security perimeter and the clean room.
我们找的芯片应该在这个中心
The stick we're looking for should be in this core.
所以我们要到那下面 拿到芯片
So we're gonna have to get underneath, extract it,
然后用个仿制品替换掉
and replace it with a decoy.
现在回到芯片上
Now, we're about to get to the chip.
这芯片很轻
This is the thing about the chip, it's very thin.
幸运的是跟扑克牌大小重量差不多
Luckily, it's similar in weight and size to a playing card,
所以我们要把飞牌技术再精进一下
so we're gonna have to brush up on our card-istry.
喔 喔
Whoa, whoa!
那样不行
That's no good.
那我们要怎么进去？哈尼斯·派克
So how do we get in? Hannes Pike.
他是南非黑帮的儿子
He's the son of a South African gangster.
跟着他来的
He's RSVP'd with what looks like
还有保镖和随从
a couple of members of his security detail.
有个博士 负责检查 我猜的 还有个叫巴菲的人
A doctor, to vet it, I guess, and somebody named Buffy.
对 而且他每周旅行都会换女人
Yeah, apparently, he travels with a different bimbo every week. Hmm.
不知道我们谁来演那个女人呢
I wonder which one of us gets to play the bimbo.
嘿 我能加入吗
Hey, can I get in?
在老虎机柔和的声音中
At the soothing sound of the slots
你进入平静的状态昏昏欲睡
you slip into a serene state of slumber and sleep.
杰克 一段时间里
Jack, for a moment,
他们会认为你是汗内斯 拖住他们
they will think you're Hannes, so lead them out and keep them busy.
他对你们无条件的信任
You trust your people implicitly.
你会让他们处理一切
You will have them take care of everything,
你会在车上等着
and you will wait in the car.
睁开眼睛 醒过来 去
And eyes open, wide awake. Go.
不好意思 这些人在跟着我
Excuse me. These people are following me.
你也许该检查一下他们的口袋
You might wanna check their pockets.
然后我们有很短的时间进入实验室
Then our time is ticking to infiltrate the lab
把芯片偷出来拿到市场上 我会交给天眼
and get the card to the market, where I'll hand it off to the Eye,
然后我们就都能回家了
so we can all get the hell home.
啊 汗内斯 老朋友 你能来真是太好了
Hannes, my old friend. So glad you could make it.
我就知道你特别钟情于老派投标
I knew you had a soft spot for an old-school bidding war.
最近怎么样？
How have you been?
我完全相信我手下的人 让他们处理
I trust my people implicitly. What they say goes.
当然 但你肯定想亲自看一看
Certainly. But I'm sure you'd like to see it for yourself.
拿在手里检查一下质量
Hold it in your hands, check the build quality.
或者不看 没关系
Or not. Also fine.
请各位跟我来
Well, if you'd like to follow me.
你们必须取下身上的金属 手表 戒指之类的
You'll have to remove all your metal. Watches, rings, etc.
- 当然 - 冒昧问一句
- Yeah, of course. - Excuse me for asking…
我以前是不是在哪见过你们？
Where might I have seen you before?
我不知道 可能是在我的座谈会上
I don't know, probably one of my many symposiums.
皮书套
The book jacket!
我得说 迈克尔拉斯基先生 我是你的忠实书迷
I have to say, Dr. Michaelakis, I'm a huge fan.
噢 非常感谢
Oh, thank you so much.
哪本书？我的书太多了
Uh, which book? There have been so many…
汗内斯经常跟你这样开玩笑吗 博士
Does Hannes' chippy always talk for you, Doctor?
医生？
Doctor?
对不起 你说玩笑 我们就总认为是说这个家伙
Sorry, when you say "chippy, " you are referring to Buffy here, yeah?
当然
Of course.
汗内斯更喜欢用「荡妇」来称他的所有小鲜肉
Hannes prefers the term "floozy" for all his boy toys.
- 对 - 记住了
- Yeah. He does. That's good. - Noted.
对了 我收到了你的邮件 迈克尔拉斯基先生
By the way, I got your email, Dr. Michaelakis.
你询问我们在温室…
You had a query about our ability
不使用稀释 冷冻和错误修正
to maintain quantum coherence at room temperature
维持量子相干性的能力提出了质疑
without the use of dilution, refrigerators, or error correction.
你可以说明一下吗？
Do you care to elucidate?
- 没错 - 是的
- Right. - Yeah.
是的 我是发过那封邮件
Yes, I did send that email.
- 那天我看到了 - 是的 我发了 说什么来着？
- The other day, I saw you. - I did, I sent it. So what gives?
抱歉 什么来着？
I'm sorry, what gives…
我想她想说的是…
I think what she's trying to say…
好了 我们专家在开会 巴菲
Actually, the grown-ups are having a meeting, Buffy.
好吧
Okay.
请你帮我拿着
If you'll hold on to that.
- 好的 没问题 博士 - 谢谢
- Yeah, sure, Doctor. - Thank you.
听着 每个七年级的学生 甚至包括哪些蠢学生
Now, every seventh grader, even the dumb ones,
都知道热力学第二定律
know the second law of thermodynamics.
「所有有序的系统 都将趋于无序状态」 无序
"All ordered systems tend toward disorder." Disorder!
所以我要再问你一次 先生 刚才说什么来着？
So I'm going to ask you one more time, sir, what gives?
这其实涉及到拓扑量子顺序
Well, it's actually topological quantum order.
是指量子效应在宏观的层面体现
The emergence of quantum effects on a macroscopic level.
这就是刚才我说的
So that is, in fact, what gives.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你知道 巴菲这名字挺适合你的
You know, Buffy is not a bad name for you.
你知道的 巴夫 费姆 陶特
You know, buff, firm, taut.
很不错 你是在哪找了本字典吗？
That's good. Did you just find a thesaurus somewhere?
努比莱
Nubile.
- 很好 谢谢你 - 好的 我们开始吧
- That's good. Thank you. - Okay. There we go.
抱歉 抱歉
Sorry, sorry.
那手杖是金属的 我们怎么带出去？
The stick's metal. How are we going to get it out?
是啊 我不知道
Yeah. I don't know.
就是这里了
This is the housing.
传输速度达到了八亿两千万量子英里
820 million qubit miles of digi-synaptic resonance.
但无疑我们独霸全球之处
But of course, what sets us apart from anything else on the planet
就是我们的处理器 我们玩笑的把它称为「魔法扫帚」
is the processor, which we playfully refer to as the Magic Broomstick.
扫帚？
The Broomstick?
有着清理地球上 任何电脑系统内容
Has the power to clear the contents of any computing system on the planet
并将其传输给你的能力
and then magically sweep them into your bin.
扫帚 真有趣
Oh! Broomstick. That's funny.
看看吧 随你怎么检查
Take a look, vet it however you'd like,
然后告诉汗内斯 我们将于周一投标
and tell Hannes we'll be taking bids on Monday.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我的天 这里面肯定 有什么东西让我过敏了
Oh, my God. I must be allergic to something in here.
你怎么可能在这里面 发生过敏反应呢？
What could you possibly be allergic to in here?
- 这房间是密封的 - 就是它
- This room is hermetically sealed. - That's it.
看来是对电子辐射过敏
I'm allergic to hermetic seals.
好的 把他扶到一边去
If we could get him away from the computer, please.
- 这是唯一的可能 - 让他恢复一下
- That's the one thing. - Just until he's recovered.
我们还需要点抗菌药…
We're gonna need some anti-baa…
这里有湿巾吗？
Do we have alcohol wipes?
如果你要靠近 就必须确保手部是无菌的
Your hands need to be sterile if you intend to get any closer.
你听明白了吗？
Do I make myself clear?
- 抱歉 我们不能… - 不 我很好
- Sorry. We couldn't… - No, I'm fine.
把这药吃了吧
…take his medicine into the country.
是的
Yeah…
不能再接触过敏源了
Can't risk any contamination.
到时候你得离它远一点
You're gonna have to stay away from the inner workings.
非常感谢 谢谢
Thank you very much. Thank you.
- 好的 如果你弄完了 - 给你
- All right. If you're done… - Oh. Here you go.
很抱歉 好的 我没事
Sorry about this. Okay. I'm okay.
他有时就会如此 很快会过去的
This happens to him sometimes. It'll pass.
过敏 你什么也做不了
Allergies. Nothing you can do.
你能做点什么 医生
Well, something you could do, Doctor.
没事了吧？
Okay?
搜他的身
Search him, please.
刚才不是搜过了吗？
Didn't we just do that?
我们什么也没做
Are you serious?
好的 我要全方位检查系统
Okay. I wanna run full diagnostics on the system.
把你的衣服脱掉
这完全没有必要
This is completely unnecessary.
快点 伸手
请抬你的手
请你转身
把手伸出来
不要乱动 别耍花样
请转身
好了 没事了
举手 举手
Up, up,
好的
Okay.
靠边走
嘿 我自己能走
Hey! I can walk on my own.
哇
Whoa!
你没事吧？
抱歉
Sorry.
你赶快抬身
起来 小姐
举手 举手
张开你的手
转身
举起手 举起手
嘿
Hey!
我自己来
I can do that myself.
我们刚认识 伙计
We just met, man.
毛手毛脚的
Handsy, handsy, handsy.
另一边
嘿
Hey!
我的眼睛在这 伙计
My eyes are up here, man.
你喜欢吗？
How do you like it?
喂 你们干嘛？
嘿 我没事
Hey, I'm good.
慢慢转个身过来
转身 伸手啊
转身
Turn around.
慢慢转身
别乱动
你这有东西吗？
Do you have anything?
我不知道 不能相信任何人
I don't know. Can't trust anybody.
- 我没事 - 他们是安全的
- I'm good. - They're clean.
没有发现
最后检查一下 然后让他们出去
Do your final checks and get them out of here.
- 好的 - 我们又走这边了
- OKay. - Oh, we're walking this way again. Yay.
我不会说话
I don't speak the language.
看到没？
See?
我怎么跟你说的？我们什么都没有
What did I tell you, man? We didn't have anything.
谢谢 伙计 非常感谢
Thanks, pal. Appreciate that.
这边有四个人要出来了 准备进行检查
这个像白色舞池的东西 让我想摆动身体
Something about a big white dance floor, makes me wanna boogie.
嘿 感谢邀请我们
Hey, thanks for having us.
那东西真不错
That's great stuff.
准备过去
好吧
Okay.
你们的安保措施 还真是严格啊
You guys are pretty serious about your security, huh?
好的
Okay.
我的东西都在吗 我觉得我进来的时候还带着更多的东西
Do I have all my things? I feel like I came in with more stuff.
都在这里了吗？
Did I come in with more stuff?
别捣乱了 快过去
你不这么想？
You don't think so?
好的 下一个
先生 我想我的钱包还在你那
Uh, sir, I think you still have my wallet.
记得吗 我进来的时候给你了
Remember, I, uh, gave it to you when I came in?
我想把它要回来
It would be nice to leave with it.
钱包要通过了
Wallet coming through.
抱歉 是我的皮带
Sorry, my belt.
呃…
Uh…
我想都在这了 对吧？
I guess that's everything, right?
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 那不是玩具 巴菲 - 抱歉
- That is not a toy, Buffy. - Sorry.
走走走
Go, go, go!
好的 在市场上放我下去
All right. Drop me off at the market
我要交给天眼
so I can get this to the Eye.
你要我在他们开始…
You asked me to call you when they started
像无头苍蝇一样跑路时打给你
running around like headless chickens.
是的 就是那么回事
Well, that's what's happening.
这就是他们说的地方？
This is where your sources told you they'd be?
不 他只是告诉我 也许能在这找到答案
No, this is where my sources said we might find an answer.
你没死啊？
你还活着？
你 做了什么好事把你放出来了？
她肯定很了解你的事
She must be familiar with your work.
打搅一下
Excuse me.
小姐 你见过这些人吗？
Miss, have you seen these people?
见过他们吗？
我的孙儿跟他
他们的头说了话
他在里边
跟我来
她说她的孙子跟他们的 老大说过话
She says her grandson spoke to their leader.
他在后面
He's in the back.
什么？
What?
不 你会说普通话？
No "Wow, you speak Mandarin"?
如果你的普通话讲的好
我会跟你讲
活该 你来不来呀
来啦
李儿
李儿你在哪里呀？
大变活人
Ah! The Coffin to the Beyond.
总是涉及到暗门 陷阱或者镜子
It was always a flap, or a trap or mirrors.
观众们认为他就那样消失了
The audience thought he'd just disappeared.
但是他总是藏在 里面的某个地方
But he was always hidden somewhere inside.
我想这就是你父亲 所做那东西的原型
I believe that's the prototype for the one your father had made.
他和那些年的很多人一样 都是从这里订做道具的
He, like many others over the years, ordered his supplies from here.
当然了
Ah! Of course.
所以当我说他们在澳门时 你给我摆脸色
That's why you gave me the look when I said they were in Macau.
你父亲在你小时候来过这里
Your father used to come here when you were young.
能给我一些空间吗？
Can I please get some space here?
你认为你是唯一一个 对所发生的事情质疑了30年的人吗？
If you think you're the only one who'd wondered for 30 years what happened…
不是的
…you're not.
莱昂内尔是魔术大师
Lionel was a master magician.
他要么在前面缠上锁链
Either he gamed the hinges,
这样就能踹开门跳出来
so he could kick the door and they would pop out,
要么使用内部的锁 这样就能开锁
or he had access to the lock from the inside so he could pick it.
人们说保险箱是廉价金属做的 所以很容易弄开
Word is the safe was made from cheap metal, and it bowed.
他总是留一手的
Still, he always had something up his sleeve.
但最后他达到了他能力的极限用尽了技巧
Unless he'd reached the limit of his capabilities and his clock ran out.
抱歉 我奶奶那儿也许有你要的东西
Excuse me. My grandmother has something you might want.
这是你父亲的
This was your father's.
他订做了几个这样的东西
He had several of these made.
你的父亲
让我把这个给你
谢谢
那么四骑士的事呢？
And the Horsemen?
我偶然听到他们谈话
I overheard them talking.
当时他们其中一个叫阿特拉斯的
One of them, Atlas,
在附近的市场上见什么人
he's meeting someone at the market nearby.
刚刚他们不是两个人吗？
（换你出招了）
至于前特工罗兹
As for former Agent Rhodes,
查清他的所在位置是我们的首要任务
his location is now your number one priority.
我们已经发布了国际通告
We're putting out an international APB.
我们需要当地部门的合作
We have Interpol, including cooperation from local authorities.
考恩特工
Agent Cowan.
我想你应该没有 进入纽堡联邦监狱
I'm assuming it was actually not you who walked into Newburgh Federal Prison,
然后三十分钟后和 撒迪厄斯·布兰德利一起离开了吧？
then walked out 30 minutes later with Thaddeus Bradley?
- 什么？- 他用了你的证件
- What? - He used your ID.
你在做什么 罗兹？
What are you doing, Rhodes?
（氹仔市场）
- 阿特拉斯 嘿 - 迪伦
- Atlas, hey. - Dylan.
- 我搞砸了 抱歉 - 你来这里做什么？
- I blew it, I'm sorry. - What are you doing here?
我是来帮忙的
I'm here to help now.
好的 我们绝对不需要你的帮助
Okay, we definitely don't need your help.
我知道我搞砸了 好吗？
I know I messed up, all right?
是的 你让大家都身陷险境
Yeah, you put everybody's lives in danger.
- 大家在哪？- 大家在哪？
- Where is everybody? - Where is everybody?
实际上不能被人看到 我和你在一起
I can't be seen with you, actually, right now.
我知道了 好吗？我很感谢
I got it now, okay? I appreciate you taking
你抽出时间 来控制一下局势
the time to take control for a little while.
- 嘿 我真的… 是吗？- 但是我知道了 好吗？
- Hey, I'm actually… Yeah? - Yeah, but I got it now, all right?
- 是吗？- 是的
- You do? - Yeah.
你看起来应该 好好的休息一下 伙计
You look like you can get some rest, buddy.
- 你在这里等谁？- 我没等任何人
- Who you meeting here? - I'm not meeting anybody.
他们告诉我你在翁氏 见了什么人
They told me at long's you were meeting somebody.
翁氏？
At long's?
好的 是的 不 我是…
Okay, yeah, no, I am, um…
我见了来自「天眼」的人
I'm meeting somebody from the Eye.
是的 他们答应我
Yeah, no, they agreed to meet me
用我们的命换这张电脑芯片
to exchange this computer chip for our lives back.
事情就是这样子
So that's what it's come to now.
我希望你对现在的状况感到开心
I hope you're happy with the situation you've put us in.
你和「天眼」谈过了？
You're talking to the Eye?
是的
Yeah.
你为何和他们谈？
Why are you talking to the Eye?
阿特拉斯 阿特拉斯 给我晶片卡
Atlas. Atlas, give me the stick.
迪伦 你已经不是我们的老大了 好吗？
Dylan, you're not our leader anymore, okay?
你不是我们的英雄 你也不是FBI
You're not our hero. You're not FBI.
你不是魔术师 你根本什么也不是
You're not a magician. You're not really anything.
我们相信了你一年
And we trusted you for a year.
所以如果你真的想帮助我们…
So if you really wanna help us… If you really…
如果你真想帮助我们 那你就离开
If you really wanna help us, you would leave.
我懂了 好的 再见
I get it. Cool. Bye.
你好 你好
Hello, hello!
是的 你在魔术店联系的 那个人就是我
Yeah, that was me you called at the magic shop.
但还是很有趣 我知道你在实验室会被我吓跑
So much fun though, knowing you'd be scurrying away from me at the lab
所以我来了这里
just to bring it to me here.
你真的认为我会让你走吗？
Did you actually think I'd let you go?
- 你是怎么做到的？- 每个人都有自己的弱点
- How did you do that? - Everyone has their button.
一旦按下去 就变瞎了 而你的弱点就是自负
You push it and they go blind. And yours, obviously, is ego.
「坚持到底
"Stay the course.
巨变即将发生
Great changes are in store.
相信你独特的才能
Trust that your unique talents
将会被人所知「
will not go unrecognized."
- 那个是你 - 是的
- That was you. - Yeah.
梅里特下载了所有的文件
Merritt downloaded all the files,
但你认为我们是 怎么找到他的呢？
but how do you think we were able to find him?
你的电话
Your phone.
我想看看幕后黑手
I asked to see the face behind all of this.
被你手机录下的 其实是平板电脑的声音
What you actually put your phone on was a bi-wave siphon pad.
又一次科学战胜了魔术
Once again, science beats magic.
- 那么 我要的东西呢？- 没在
- So, the stick? - No.
在我这
I got it.
在我这 在我这
I got it. I got it.
- 该死 迪伦 - 等等 别管他们
- Fuck, Dylan! - Wait, leave them!
你真以为我会就那样离开？
You really think I'm gonna walk away from you?
给我晶片卡
Give me the stick!
给我
Give me it!
好的 别再质疑我 滚开
All right. Don't ever question me again. Beat it!
- 好的 东西给我 - 去死吧
- So, the stick. - Go to hell.
各位
Boys.
抱歉 抱歉
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
你们可有不少人
There's like 10 of you.
拜托 他只是在耍小伎俩
Come on, he's just doing tricks.
他在那 快去
He's there! Go!
迪伦 看着这会飞的小鸟 睡着吧
Dylan, watch the pretty birdies fly. And sleep.
- 对我可没用 - 难道就不能让你分心吗？
- Doesn't work on me. - Not even as a distraction?
- 干的好 - 还是自己动手好
- Good job. - Nice to be involved.
嘿 各位 各位 嘿
Hey, guys! Guys! Hey!
- 我刚才见到了迪伦 出事了 - 你说这话是什么意思？
- I just saw Dylan, something happened. - What do you mean you just saw Dylan?
迪伦在这里？发生什么了？
Dylan's here? What happened?
- 阿特拉斯 - 我不知道 我不知道
- Atlas. - I don't know.
他们在做什么？
What are they doing?
那些是沃尔特的人
Those are Walter's men.
这就是他们要的
This is what they want.
搞什么？怎么还在你手上？
What the hell? How do you still have that?
那是莱昂内尔·施莱克的保险箱
Whoa. That's Lionel Shrike's safe.
他们要用那个做什么？
What the hell do they want with that?
好的 我们得跟着那卡车
Okay, we gotta follow that truck.
迪伦肯定在他们手上 我们的时间不多
They must have Dylan. We don't have much time.
你要什么？
What do you want?
你知道一些非常重要的事情
You to understand something very important.
我们是镜像
We are mirror images.
你看 和你一样
You see, because like you,
我和我父亲 有着很深的联系
I share a very deep connection with my father.
而且和你一样 我将不惜一切代价为他进行复仇
And like you, I'll stop at nothing to avenge any wrongs done to him.
你知道你父亲和我父亲 唯一的区别吗？
You know the only difference between your father and mine?
我父亲还活着
Mine's still alive.
让他起来
Get him up.
那么 就是这个人
So, this is the man
花了一辈子时间暗算我
who spent a lifetime plotting against me.
即使你的巨幅海报挂在 我的卧室窗户外面
I wouldn't have known your face
我也认不出来你是谁
if it had been on a billboard outside my bedroom window.
但你却花了30年时间一直算计我？
But you have spent, what, 3O years thinking about mine?
当我父亲死的时候
When my father died,
你的保险公司 拒绝了我母亲的请求
your insurance company denied my mother her claims.
- 她穷苦而死 - 我甚至不知道…
- I wouldn't even have known… - She died a pauper!
你的母亲是谁
…who your mother was.
她只是个数字 一连串资料的十亿分之一
She was a digit, a nanobyte in a stream of data.
因为你不关心任何事
Because nothing is personal to you
任何人和任何事对于 你来说都只是数字 对吧？
and everyone and everything is just a number, isn't that so?
那正是你错的地方 罗兹先生
That is where you are wrong, Mr. Rhodes.
一旦你出名了 那就跟你有关了
Once you made yourself known it became very personal.
- 我的儿子… - 是的 反社会的家伙
- My son… - Yeah, the sociopath.
有趣的是 我有七个所谓的婚生子女
Funny thing is, I have seven so-called legitimate children.
他们虚情假意 十分势力 而且愚蠢无比
Sniveling, snobbish, stupid runts.
但我有一个和我一样的私生子
I have one illegitimate child who is a lot like me.
问题是 他想要一些东西
The point is, he wants something,
像那些好的父母一样 我将不惜一切代价让他获得
and like any good parent, I will stop at nothing to get it for him.
那东西就在你的骑士身上
Your Horsemen have it.
你会把它和他们 现在就交给我们
You will turn it and them over to us, now.
不
No.
迪伦 我很希望你好好记住这一刻
Dylan, I would like you to really take this moment in
因为这就是你一心报私仇
because this is the consequence of your personal vendetta come to life
反被将了一军的结果
and staring you in the face.
我要你知道就算你归西
I want you to know that when you're gone,
我们也不会停止
we're not going to stop.
我们将毁了你相信的一切
We're gonna destroy everything you believe in,
先从四骑士开始 最后毁了「天眼」
starting with the Horsemen, and ending with the Eye.
现在 鼓起你的勇气
Now then, cast your mind back
站在这亲眼目睹你父亲失败
to standing by the banks of the river watching your father descend,
遭遇耻辱并名誉扫地的河岸边
disgraced and discredited.
这些年来你感受到的恐惧
The horrid psychic pain as you have relived for years.
我感受到同样的感觉 两年前你不仅毁了
I felt that same thing two years ago
我父亲的前途 还有他的尊严
as you drained not just my father's fortune, but his dignity!
而你却从中得到快乐
And yet you took pleasure from it.
这应该能给你带回一些童年记忆
This should bring back some childhood memories.
- 想喝点茶吗？- 谢谢你
- Would you like some tea? - Oh. Thank you.
- 你准备好了吗？- 请便
- You ready? - Over to you.
水花
Splash!
完事了
Job done!
看起来还得等不少时间
Hell is going to seem like a day at the spa
到时候我们就把骑士灭了
by the time we're through with these Horsemen.
- 你说呢？- 完全正确
- Wouldn't you say? - You had me at "hell."
我非常爱你
I love you so much.
我每次都会给自己留一手的
Always keep something up my sleeve.
我希望我能洗净自己的灵魂
I wish I could dredge from the muck of my soul
让它毫无污秽 但这是不可能的
one speck of remorse, but I can't.
所以我会继续做着生意 并试着别笑得太明显
So I'll stick to the business at hand and try not to smile too broadly.
还有 谢谢你 为我送来迪伦·罗兹先生
And, uh, thank you for delivering Mr. Dylan Rhodes.
我想这事已经完了
I take it it's done.
差不多沉睡在海底了
Literally hit the bottom.
- 那么 四骑士在哪？- 他们只是表演的
- Now, where are the Horsemen? - They're performers.
他们的骄傲和自负 他们对于名气的渴望 实在是太强烈了
Their pride, their ego, their need to be adored are all too powerful
他们无法隐藏太久
to keep them out of the limelight for long.
如果找不到他们 你就会发现你自己
If they don't make themselves known, you will find yourself
和罗兹先生一样 处于一个十分相似的情况
in a very similar position to Mr. Rhodes.
- 清楚了吗？- 像他沉入的水一样清楚
- Are we clear about that? - As clear as the water he's under.
抓住骑士之后 再给你剩下的
You'll have the rest when I have the Horsemen.
迪伦
Dylan!
迪伦 拜托 醒醒伙计
Dylan, come on, buddy, breathe!
- 迪伦 - 迪伦
- Dylan. - Dylan?
迪伦 醒醒
Dylan, come on!
你没事
You're okay.
天啊 你吓坏我们了 伙计
Jesus! You scared the hell out of us, man.
- 你没事吧 伙计？- 好了
- Are you all right, bro? - Okay!
- 谢谢你 - 这是我起码能做的
- Thank you! - This is the least I could do.
不 你本可以袖手旁观的
No. There's a hell of a lot less you could've done.
我们可不会那样
That was not an option.
你为我们挡了子弹 那可是大恩情
You took a bullet for us, it was huge.
你真的做到了 伙计
You really did, man.
说真的 感谢你们救我出来
Thanks for pulling me out. Seriously.
好啊
Yeah.
是你自己出来的 我们只是拉你出水
You got yourself out. We did the easy part.
是真的 因为我当时 只是站在岸边
Literally, in my case, I was just standing on the shore
是阿特拉斯跳下水 找到你的
while Atlas jumped down and got you.
我说真的
I'm serious.
嘿 各位 有点不对劲
Hey, you guys. Something's not right.
- 怎么了？- 怎么？
- What's wrong? - What?
- 这是假的 - 什么？
- It's fake. - What?
不 我拿到了芯片
No, I had the stick.
是真的芯片 我发誓是真的 就在我手里
The actual stick. I swear, it was in my hand,
然后我把它放在一个小盒子里
in the lab, and then I put it in the little case thing.
- 然后给了阿特拉斯 - 对 后来我交给迪伦
- And I gave it to Atlas. - Right, which I then gave to Dylan.
有没有可能 是你错放在什么地方了？
Is there any chance you've possibly misplaced it at any point?
不 我从你手里把它拿走
No, I took it from you and then slipped it back in your coat
然后把你推开时又还给了你
when I pushed you out.
总之 我们这次算是栽了
Either way, we're left holding a whole sack full of nada.
是的 但他们还是会认为 东西就在我们手上
Yeah, but they're gonna come after us as if we do have something.
不 好的 我同意有人 战胜了我们
No. Okay. I agree that somebody got the better of us. Okay? Somehow.
但是我不认为我们就一败涂地了
But I don't agree that we have a sack full of nada.
因为我们都在这 这才是最重要的
Because we're all here. That's a sack full of something.
听着 我们都知道沃尔特 不得到芯片不会停手
Listen, we all know that Walter is not going to stop until he gets that chip.
而且我们是唯一 知道他还活着的人
And we're the only ones that even know that he's alive.
我们不能就这样不管了 这可不是骑士的风格
We can't just walk away. That's not what the Horsemen do.
有一段话
There's a quote. Um…
这话是一个魔术师说的
It's actually by the magician
正是他让我走上了这条路
that made me wanna do this in the first place.
说的是…
It's, uh…
「魔术师最大的力量 永远深藏于他的空拳」
"A magician's greatest power lies forever shrouded in his empty fist."
「然而他能说服世人」
"And the very idea that he can convince the world
「他确实握有秘密」
that he is, in fact, carrying with him a secret."
- 那是莱昂内尔·施莱克说的 - 是的
- That's Lionel Shrike. - Right.
那你的意思是我们
So what are you saying?
要假装我们手头有没有的东西？
That we should pretend like we have something we don't?
（愚者）
- 沃尔特最大的恐惧是什么？- 被曝光
- What is Walter's greatest fear? - Being seen.
- 那芯片是做什么的？- 那芯片可以破译一切
- And what does the stick do? - The stick can unencode anything.
它可以悄然入侵这星球上的任何一台电脑
It can open up a back door into any computer on the planet.
- 包括他的 - 是的
- Including his. - Yeah.
好的 我们不仅要让他认为 芯片在我们手上
Right, we not only make him think that we have it,
还要让他以为我们将用 芯片将他彻底毁了
but that we're going to use it to expose and destroy him.
我们需要个计划 但我们没时间了
We need a plan. But we don't have time.
我们还有彼此 而且我们有五个人
We have each other and there are five of us.
但是我们还需要惊喜 对吧？还有必要的道具和资源
But we also need supplies, right? And resources.
或者更多的人
And probably more than five people.
你真认为没人帮你们？
Do you really think you don't have help?
她会说英语 当然了 对
Oh, she speaks English. Of course. Yeah.
你知道为何「愚者」是 塔罗牌中力量最大的？
Do you know why the Fool is the most powerful card in the tarot?
不是因为抽到它的人就是愚者
Not because the person who draws him is a fool.
他愚 因为他是一张白纸
He's a fool because he's a clean slate,
因此可以成为 无所不能
and, therefore, can become anything.
你们是被选择的人
You were chosen.
你们都是
All of you.
不是因为你们是谁 而是因为你们将取得的成绩
Not because of who you are, but because of who you might become.
当你说「被选择」 你是「天眼」的一部分？
When you say "chosen"… Are you part of the Eye?
是的 我们是「天眼」的一部分
Yes. We are part of the Eye.
你们都怀疑我们的存在
You've each doubted our existence.
想知道 我们是否在观察
Wondering if we, indeed, were watching.
我们确实在观察 我们一直如此
We are. We always have been.
这可是世界上最好的魔术店
This is the best magic shop in the world.
- 你明白她说的 对吧？- 是的
- You know what she's saying, right? - Yes.
现在我们有了资源和帮手
That now we have resources and help.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那么 谁加入？
So, who's in?
- 我加入 - 是的 我加入
- I'm in. - Yeah, I'm in.
我们开干吧
Let's do this.
- 干杯 - 干杯
（你看了这个吗？）
不 不 不
No, no, no.
不久前 我们被人耍了
Not long ago, we were tricked.
我被人发现没有死去
I was exposed and brought back from the dead.
所以我们觉得唯一的办法
So we thought it was only fitting that we do the same thing
- 就是以牙还牙 - 除夕 午夜 伦敦
- to the person who did it to us. - Midnight, New Year's Eve. London.
我们将进行一连串的表演 那将会是我们的绝唱
We will be performing a series of shows that all connect to our big finale,
所以你们得好好看着
so pay close attention to each trick.
叫我父亲来
Get my father.
快点
Run!
我要找国际刑警 苏格兰场 能找的帮手都找上
I want Interpol, Scotland Yard, whoever we have in London.
罗兹方面有什么消息？
What do we know about Rhodes?
不管骑士们在哪 他都会在那里
Wherever the Horsemen are, that's where he is.
我们去机场吧
Let's get to the airport.
留小孩在家 准备享受疯狂夜晚
So leave your kiddies at home and get ready for a wild night,
因为我们也会让某人死而复生
because we, too, will bring someone back from the dead.
各位行动吧
Let's move, everyone!
在世界最大的舞台前面…
In front of the largest stage in the world…
真实的世界
The actual world.
你知道他们在耍你 对吧？把你引入陷阱
You know they're playing you, right? Leading you into a trap?
是的 但这威胁是真的
Yeah, but the threat is real.
这张芯片可以黑进 地球上任何的电脑 包括我们的
This card can hack into any system on the planet, including ours.
现在芯片在他们手上 他们为何就不会用？
They have it, why wouldn't they use it to expose us?
我 我们所做的一切
Me. Everything we've done.
这是真的吗 麦金尼先生？
Is it real, Mr. McKinney?
这威胁是真的
The threat is real.
那么 我们要怎么对付他们？
So, how do we stay ahead of them?
我们得在午夜赶到伦敦
We need to get to London by midnight.
我们现在在伦敦
We are here in London
除夕夜充满了人群
on this New Year's Eve, and the crowds are out in force.
当地人和游客们
Locals and tourists alike
准备好参加年度大派对了
getting ready for the party of the year.
一段跟四骑士有关的视频
A video gone viral from the infamous
已经在网上疯传了
Horsemen magicians has surfaced.
他们承诺会盛大复出
They promise to make a grand reappearance.
但结局会是他们在全国电视上被捕或证明清白？
But will it end in their arrest on national television?
或者说只是一个噱头？
Or some sort of vindication?
天晓得他们会在哪里出现
Who knows where they'll show up…
但我们知道不管何时何地
remake reporter H But we do know, wherever,
人们会拭目以待
whenever that is, people will be watching.
是的 短信 推特 博客
Yeah, texts, tweets, lnstagrams.
任何和骑士有关系的消息
Anything that says "Horsemen, " brags about seeing the Horsemen,
都给我跟一跟
tag them and bundle them.
爸爸 这一次担任保安的是谁 是你们吗？
Dad, who do we have security-wise on this? Your guys?
你要谁都行
Whoever you want.
都带上 再加上一些人
Well, we want all of them and all their friends.
让任何想赚外快的人随时待命
Anyone who wants to work stationed throughout the city,
60秒立即出现在全市各处
so they can be anywhere in 60 seconds.
你好 嘿
Hello! Hey!
我叫杰克·怀尔德
My name's Jack Wilder.
该死的 回来的感觉真好
Goddamn, it feels good to be back.
好的 都过来吧
All right, gather around. Indulge me.
我要跟你们分享一些消息
I wanna talk to you about something real quick.
你们都知道三张扑克戏法 也被叫做「找小姐」戏法吗？
You all know Three Card Monte, also known as "Find the Lady"?
在全世界由老千表演的戏法 为什么是老千？
Trick performed by street hustlers all over the world. And why street hustlers?
因为只要你靠近桌子 你就输了
Because as soon as you walk up to the table, you lose.
每次都是如此 让我示范一遍
Every time. Let me demonstrate.
在此期间 我们找一个活生生的女王
While we're at it, let's find ourselves a life-sized Queen.
女士 你能当我的女王吗？
Ma'am, would you mind being my Queen?
别担心 我向你保证 回来的机会是五成
Don't worry. I promise you there's a 50 percent chance
表演结束后你活着
you'll get her back after the show.
到那边去 非常感谢
Head over there. Thank you very much.
好的 我们来找一些 服侍女王的杰克吧
All right. Let's find ourselves some Jacks to serve our Queen!
相信我 先生们
Trust me, gentlemen.
我知道了这些家伙的计划 他们先是开玩笑
I know how these guys work now. They're gonna start with a tease.
来点暖场
A few little pop-ups.
弄点手段引诱你加入
Something to lure you in. Like…
你知道 就像他们现在表演的节目
Well, you know, like Three Card Monte, where the guy goes,
「看这里 但是不 不 看这里」
"Looky here, but no, no, looky here!"
当那些技巧弄完后
Except when all these little tricks are done,
你将看到的唯一东西
the only thing you're gonna be looking at
就是让你感到吃惊的
is the inside of your own colon, with the words
写着「骑士」的卡片
"Horsemen" written all over it.
还是通红的
In blood.
我们收到图像了 麦金尼先生
We get the picture, Mr. McKinney.
别再坐我的椅子
And get out of my chair.
大家好啊
Hello, everybody!
靠近一点 来呀
Come close, come on!
好的 好的 听着
All right, all right, so listen.
今晚 我将利用真实的魔术飞起来
Tonight, I am going to make something fly using actual magic.
- 准备好了吗？- 是的
- Are you ready? - Yeah!
我要利用一辆大型的船
I'm going to take a very large vessel,
我要让它飞起来 然后在泰晤士河着陆
I'm gonna make it fly over there and land on the Thames.
你能接受吗？
Can you handle that?
和以前的规则一样
Same rules apply as before.
你们要做的就是仔细看着皇后
All you need to do is keep your eye on the Queen.
就那么简单
It's as simple as that.
- 你们准备好了吗？- 是的
- Are you guys ready? - Yeah!
爸爸 看看这个
Dad, look at this.
这消息是从哪来的
Tag this one. Where does it come from?
河边 看来表演开始了
Near the river. Looks like the shows are starting.
但发现他们的不止我们
But we're not the only ones who found them.
- 什么意思？- 在一号频道
- What do you mean? - It's on Channel One.
- 转到第2频道 - 找到了
- Let's go to 2. - Here we go.
找到他了 他在这
Got him. We have a location.
是杰克·怀尔德 骑士出现了
It's Jack Wilder. Here come the Horsemen.
好的 行动 行动 行动
Okay, we're moving. Let's go, let's go.
正在比对
Typing in grid coordinates now.
转身 藏在牌后面
Turn around. Hide yourselves with the cards.
我们开始了 交换
And here we go. Switch!
你们还盯着她吗？要我去后面看看吗？
You guys still have your eye on her? You want me to go back and do it?
好的 我继续 交换
Okay, all right. I'm moving on. And switch.
她在哪？
Where is she?
那边 你们确定？
Down at the end? You sure?
好的 后面的伙计 能击鼓吗？
All right, can I get a drumroll from my man in the back?
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
她在那
There's my girl.
不是我的姑娘 是你的姑娘
Not my girl, 100 percent your girl.
但在这样的情况下
But just in this situation.
好的 但我得先暖暖场 好吗？
Okay, but I gotta warm up a little bit first. Okay?
那么 我们先飞点小东西 比如…
So, uh, let me just make something small fly, like…
飞飞飞
Fly, fly, fly!
对吧 看看啊 拜托 伙计们
Wow, right? Look at that! Aw. Come on, people.
真无情 你 飞起来
Tough crowd. You, fly!
- 我？- 看看你的衣服里
- Me? - Check your fly.
你们喜欢吗？
You like that?
你们接受这个设定
You support that relationship?
那家伙的裤子里藏着鸽子 真是太恶心了
That guy had a bird in his pants. That's disgusting.
收到 我们收到了两份报告
Copy that. We've got two sightings reported.
- 正在前往格林威治市场 - 给我找撒迪厄斯
- Heading to Greenwich Market. - Get me Thaddeus.
撒迪厄斯 FBI来了 他们已经行动了
Thaddeus, the FBI are here. They're moving.
让他们去吧 那正中四骑士的下怀
Let 'em move. That's what the Horsemen want.
要是他们先赶到？那就惨了
Well, what if they get there first? That can't happen.
我保证他们找不到的
I guarantee you, they won't.
找到他们的所在
Find the pattern.
只有这样 你才能在它们开始
You do that, and you'll be able to cut them off
最后的表演前阻止他们
before they get to their final trick.
如果你想更放心的话 我来替你摆平FBI
If it makes you feel better, I'll take care of the FBI.
我想你找到我了
OK, well, I guess you found me!
第三个找到了
We've got a third spot.
好的 各位 我们有模型了
Okay, everybody, we're getting a pattern.
调到二频道 13和21
Um… Give me two, 13 and 21.
那是什么？暂停 放大
What the hell is that? Freeze that and zoom in.
这是怎么回事？
How the hell did this happen?
他死了 我们看着他沉下去 这怎么可能？
He's dead. We watched him drown. How the hell did this happen?
现在就先接受现实 目前最首要的问题是
Given that it did happen, the pertinent question is,
我们要怎么办？
what are we gonna do about it?
我们要阻止他 爸爸 我们要阻止他
We're gonna stop him, Dad. We'll stop him.
我的外套在哪？
Where's my coat?
沃尔特 恕我直言 我从来没看好过保险箱
Walter, for the record, I never loved the safe idea.
我知道他们去哪了
Oh, I know where they're going.
接下来的表演是梅里特的 地点就在河边
The next show is Merritt's and it's by the river.
我们得找到他
Chase, you need to get to him
这样就能 找到骑士 并阻止他们之后的行动
so we can find the Horsemen's entry point for the finale.
我要忏悔 据说我有一些控制方面的问题
I have a confession to make. I've been told I have some control issues.
我很努力的学着如何控制人
I've learned that it's really, really hard to control people,
所以我将试着控制一些 比人简单的多的东西
so I'm gonna try to control something that's a lot easier than people.
我要试着控制天气
I'm gonna try to control the weather.
是的 雨水
Yeah, rain, um…
要让天下雨有点困难 对吧？
It'd be a little difficult to make it rain, right?
那是只有神能做到的事情 对吧？
That would be something that only God can do, right?
我要做一些连神也做不到的事情
I'm gonna do something that God can't do.
我不仅仅要让雨停
I'm not just gonna make it clear up. No, no, no.
我要让它完全停止
I'm gonna make it actually stop.
神能做到那些吗？嗯 不 我想不能
And can God do that? Mmm. No, I don't think so.
那么让它上升呢？
Or what about make it go up?
你们还在看吗？
Are you still with me?
看着 王后在左边 开始吧 转身
Watch the Queen on the left. Let's do it. Turn around.
交换
Switch!
告诉我女士在哪
Show me the lady.
告诉我在哪
Show me the lady!
这边 这边？
The end? End?
你知道吗？我开始觉得不太妙了
You know what? I'm actually starting to feel kinda bad.
这是因为我能确实感受到 你们很专心
It's just because I can actually feel that you guys are paying attention.
但是
It's just that…
你知道 很不幸的是 你们都错了
You know, it's unfortunate that it's the wrong kind of attention.
是的 我们需要更新的鸟
Yeah, we need a fresher bird.
它真可爱 真可爱
He's so cute. He's so cute!
杀了它吧 好吗？
Let's kill him, right?
- 梅里特 就位 - 知道了 迪伦
- Merritt, move into position. - Got it, Dylan.
我在路上 我们在那见
Uh, I'm on my way. I'll see you there.
鲁拉 待命 好吗？
Lula, stand by, all right?
那么就那样… 我不知道 疯狂起来如何？
Or, what about just go, I don't know, just go insane?
伦敦各地发来报告
Reports are coming in from all over London
就好像骑士为了表演 接管了整座城市
as the Horsemen appear to have taken over the whole city for their show.
嘿 伙计 你这是去哪？
Hey, broski-whaddya-knowski? Where you headed?
- 拜托 伙计 别这么做 - 你去哪？
- Please, bro, don't do this. - Where are you headed?
北 南 东
North, south, east?
东 伦敦塔？
East. Tower of London?
塔桥还是塔桥附近？泰晤士河
Tower Bridge? Near Tower Bridge? The Thames!
你要去泰晤士河 你真容易得手
You're going to the Thamesy-Whemsy! You're so easy!
伙计 如果我们能交个朋友的话
Bro, if there's any chance of us ever having a relationship…
不可能的 你的入口在哪？
There's not. Where's your entry?
南岸？格林威治？格林威治
South Bank? Greenwich? Greenwich.
我知道你要去哪 我知道你要…
I know where you're going. I know where…
小心点 混蛋
Watch it, hobo.
嘿 梅里特 拜托 告诉我你在开玩笑 如何了？
Hey, Merritt. Oh, come on. Tell me you're kidding. How?
什么时候？
When?
该死 好的 好的 我知道了
Shit. All right. All right, I got it.
别担心 我会警告他们
Don't worry about it. I'll warn the others.
抱歉 只是…
Sorry. Just…
什么？我告诉过你们…
What? I just told you…
来电话了
Phone call.
- 喂？- 鲁拉
- Hello? - Lula.
迪伦 是的 我现在有点忙呢
Dylan. Ah, yeah, kind of in the middle of something right now.
赶紧完事 来集合地见我
Wrap it up. Meet me at the rendezvous point now.
- 什么？- 马上
- What? - Now!
那是神的举动吗？
Was that an act of God?
不 不 不 那是我的举动
No. No, no, no, that was an act of me
还有闪光灯 还有降雨机
and the strobe lights and rain machines.
我希望你们注意
And I hope you guys were paying attention.
因为这是到了最后 你们得知道的
Because you're gonna need to know all of that for the final.
那么 我是怎么做到的 我有使用隐形门帘？
So how did I do it? Did I use a Barry Trap?
也许是一些开关或者复制品？
Maybe some switches or a few duplicates?
杰克 闪人
Jack, go now!
知道吗？我也不想这么说
You know what? I hate to say it.
你们得自己找出来 我知道
You're gonna have to wait to find out. I know.
抱歉 抱歉 我也爱你们
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I love you all.
鲁拉 闪人
Lula, go!
我得走了
I have to go.
让开 FBI 走走走 让开
Out of the way, FBI! Move, move, move! Go!
派人去停车场
Get some men in that park!
赶紧去
Men in the park, now!
你要吃开胃菜？
You gonna fill up on appetizers?
还是等着吃大餐？
Or save room for the main course?
骑士在哪？
Where the hell are the Horsemen?
你们这样大张旗鼓
You can chase them all you want,
只会让他们防备
you're just gonna wind up holding your own tails.
或者你可以让他们 自己找上你们
Or, you can let them come to you.
你们要怎么做？
So, what's it gonna be?
追赶他们？
Chase them?
还是跟我打个商量？
Or make a deal with me?
又来？我们怎么又被发现了？
Again? How did we get found out again?
没事的 没事的 我们只要表演最后的节目
It's fine, it's fine. We'll just cut to the finale.
- 梅里特在哪？- 好吧 我不知道
- Where's Merritt? - Fine. I don't know.
我在这
I'm here.
- 鲁拉在哪？- 我在这
- Where's Lula? - I'm right here!
发生什么事了？
What the hell happened?
- 我的兄弟出现了 - 别担心
- My goddamn brother happened. - Don't worry about it.
我们只要去目的地
We just gotta get to the destination.
- 鲁拉 你会骑那个吗？- 我完全会骑
- Lula, can you handle that thing? - I can ride it.
你是问他们 还是仅仅问我？
Have you asked the guys that question, or just me?
- 是的 说的好 - 我们走
- Yeah, good point. - Let's go!
不 杰克
No, Jack.
该死
Shit!
杰克被抓了 我们得救他
Jack's down. We gotta get him.
来吧 快点
Come on, move!
- 杰克 走 走 - 那是刹车
- Jack! Go, go! - That's the brake.
那是油门 你会明白的
That's the gas. You'll figure it out.
来吧 跟我来
Come on, follow me!
就这样？
That's it?
- 嘿 准备好了吗？- 是的
- Hey, ready? - Yeah!
上车
Get on.
- 好的 - 好的 各位 我来了
- Yeah! - Okay, guys, I'm coming!
天啊
Whoa! Jesus!
我来了
I'm coming!
- 起来 快点 - 好的
- Get up! Come on! - Okay.
好的 你抓到我了
You got me.
那东西实在是太危险了
Those things are really dangerous!
- 快点 - 走吧
- Come on! - Go!
让他进去 快走
Get him in! Move it!
怎么了？
What is happening?
他们在哪？
Where are they?
他们随时会出现
They should be arriving any second.
只要他们午夜前到就行
That is, if they're gonna get here by midnight.
好的 感受恐惧吧
Okay, feeling fear.
恐惧 愤怒 愤怒
Fear. Anger, anger.
- 满座了 - 够了
- Oh, full house! - That's enough.
我完了
I was done.
再次见到你们真好
So nice to see you all again.
但既然我们是老朋友 我们就别废话了
But since we're such old friends, let's skip the formalities.
你们其中一个人 有着我们需要的东西
One of you has something we require.
把它交出来
So give it over.
真没有？
Nothing at all?
真的吗？
Really?
坐下
Sit down!
我们走 我们走
Let's go, let's go!
快点
别给他们任何 机会做任何事
Hurry up and move them quickly before they can do anything.
不要照着我
Get those lights off me!
上飞机
Get on the plane!
嘿
Ow! Hey!
上飞机
Get on the plane!
- 嘿 - 喔 喔 嘿
- Hey! - Whoa, whoa, hey!
是的 马上起飞
Yeah, uh, take off immediately.
你知道 这事情太简单了
You know, you make it almost too easy?
我是说 即使你们刷了些手段让你们的行踪不可捉摸
I mean, even your hilarious attempts to make yourselves unpredictable,
每次都让人找错
just follow the same pattern each time.
诡计 诡计 诡计
Set up, set up, set up.
大爆料
Big reveal.
今晚的大戏会在午夜整点
Which tonight was going to be stroke of midnight,
泰晤士河的中间？跟我说说吧
middle of the Thames? Tell me if I'm warm.
会有巨大揭露的 而且是马上上演
Well, there will be a big reveal, and it will come now.
芯片 乖小子
The stick, dear boy.
- 不 - 很好
- No. - Fine.
从她开始
Start with her.
嘿 嘿 嘿
Whoa, whoa, hey, hey, hey!
- 给他 - 丹尼 把芯片给他
- Give it to him. - Danny, give him the card.
- 给他吧 - 丹尼 拜托
- Just give it to him. - Danny, come on.
我们得仔细看看
We'll have a closer look.
好的 我欠你一个道歉
Okay, I owe you an apology.
领袖 你应该计划逃脱 好吗？
Leader, you should have planned an escape, okay?
- 这是我们俩的事 - 好的 我们两的事
- This is the both of us. - Okay, it's the both of us.
- 各位 拜托 - 拜托 别吵了
- Guys, come on! - Come on, stop!
- 你 我救了你的小女友 - 救了我的…
- You, to save your little girlfriend! - To save my…
- 有人用刀逼着她 - 我是骑士之一 你这混蛋
- He had a knife to her head! - I'm a Horseman, you dick!
好的 知道吗？现在不适合说这个
All right, you know what? This is not the time!
还有你 你到底瞒着什么？
And you, what's your deal, man?
听着 我们根本不会流血
Look, they're not gonna get blood all over the seats.
他们也许只会 把我们从飞机上丢下去
They're probably gonna throw us out of the plane.
- 是吗？- 很抱歉打断你们
- Really? - I'm sorry to interrupt,
但是我得说恭喜你们
but I just have to say congratulations.
谢谢你们
And thank you!
是真的
It's real.
什么？
What?
是真的？
It's real?
把他们带过来
Bring them through.
你说那是真的？
Did you say it's real?
他什么意思？
What is he talking about?
走
Move!
干的好 孩子
Well done, my boy.
度玛丽苏香槟
Cote Du Marisule champagne.
这是地球上最贵的一瓶了
It's the most expensive bottle on Earth.
120万美金
$1.2 million.
这是我特意为现在准备的
And I saved it just for this occasion.
说实话你这酒最多值个七万
Honestly, same bottle, Liquor Shack, 700K.
嘿你得到了你想要的
Hey. You got what you wanted.
那么 你愿意放了我们？
So, does this mean you're letting us go?
根据你对我们的了解 我们不会放人
Knowing what you know about us? No.
- 你确定？- 沙斯 我们该怎么办？
- You sure? - Chase, what shall we do?
把他们扔出去
Toss them out.
大家快速说遗言吧
Get your last words in quickly, everybody!
- 不 拜托 不要 - 永别了
- No! Come on! No! - Farewell.
天啊 不
Oh, God! No!
等等 我只想说
Wait! I just wanna say…
我投胎投错了人家
I came into the world with the wrong family,
但我遇到了正确的朋友们
but I'm leaving with the right one.
我爱你们
I love you guys!
- 不 - 不 不 不
- No! - No, no, no!
我就是这样把你踢出来的
This is how I kicked you out of the womb.
不
No!
下一个是谁？
Who's next?
不 等等 放开我
No, wait! Let me go!
放开我
Let go of me!
不 不 不
No, no, no!
- 放开我 - 把她扔出去
- Let me go! - Toss her!
我的天
Oh, God!
赶紧搞定 把门关上 这里面好冷
Hurry up and shut that door! It's getting cold in here.
好的 上路了 杰克
Okay, hit the road, Jack!
不 不 不
No, no, no!
头脑发达 四肢简单
A lot of brain, but not enough brawn.
真有趣
Oh, that was fun!
干杯 干的好 我的孩子
Cheers! Well done, my boy.
不 真是那味道吗？
No, is it supposed to taste like that?
不 不是的
No, it is not.
到底怎么回事？
What the hell is going on?
好的 来接他们吧
Okay, come pick them up!
- 快点 - 快出来
- Come on. - Come on out.
女士们先生们 四骑士
Ladies and gentlemen… The Horsemen!
不 你应该感觉很好的 伙计
No, you should feel pretty good about yourself, man.
你预料的很正确 泰晤士河 午夜时分
You predicted it correctly. The Thames, stroke of midnight.
除夕夜 新年快乐
New Year's Eve. Happy New Year!
难以置信
Unbelievable!
- 都变了 - 我们正在行动
- We are moving now. - The whole thing just changed.
- 后备待命 - 开始行动
- All backup into position stat! - We're on the move.
- 你留在这 - 当然了
- You're staying here! - Of course.
行动 行动 让开
Move! Move! Out of the way!
非常感谢 伦敦
Wow! Thank you very much, London!
我们不仅要感谢我们的老朋友 亚瑟·特雷斯勒
We would like to acknowledge not just our old friend, Arthur Tressler.
还有他年轻而帅气的儿子沃尔特·马布里
But his young and very brilliant son, Walter Mabry.
他很好的进行了一场 在我们看来十分优秀的
Who has performed one of the greatest feats of illusion
催眠表演
even we have ever seen.
他难以置信的死而复生了
He has, amazingly, brought himself back from the dead!
但是在他做这些之前
But before he did that,
他揭秘了一些人
he revealed someone.
我想我们有权利给他一个适当的介绍
And we think it only right to give him a proper introduction.
他是我们的朋友和领袖迪伦·施莱克
He is our friend and he is our leader. Dylan Shrike!
- 过来 - 是的
- Get over here! - Yeah!
那么 一般来说
So, normally
只有魔术师本人 他的助手 以及几个舞台助手
only the magician, his assistant, and a few trusted stage hands
知道一个把戏的秘密
know the secret of a trick.
但是今晚 在这样的影响下
But tonight, however, in this effect,
在泰晤士河附近的人们
all of you people around the Thames here.
因为我们还活着 所以世界各地的人们
And since we're streaming live, everyone around the world
都知道了一切
already knows everything.
只有站在那边的伙计们还不明白
And only these fellows here are the ones left in the dark.
所以我们就让你们 见识一下我们的表演
So let's see how closely you were watching our shows.
记得当我们在表演「找小姐」的时候
Remember when we were playing "Find the Lady, " and I said
我说我们使用隐形门帘
that we used a Barry Trap.
一些经典交换或分身？
Some classic switches and a few duplicates?
所以我们换了卡车的司机
Well, that's how we switched the driver of the truck.
然后我们进了早就 设计好的飞机库
Which took us to a duplicate hangar
我们利用你们的着急
where we used your need to rush,
以及怕被发现的心里 配合我们的工作
and your fear of being seen let you do the work for us.
不要用灯照着我
Get those lights off me!
那么 那架飞机 我们怎么让它飞起来的？
So, the airplane. How did we get it to fly?
我们利用的是风扇 还有灯光和造雨机
Well, we used fans, and lights and rain machines.
很明显 这一切的前提就是 我们得被你们抓住
Obviously, all of this was reliant on us getting caught.
但是我们得确保
But we needed to make sure
你们抓住我们后完全按照我们的
that you would do exactly what we needed you to do
安排来
once you did catch us.
我的弟弟沙斯 他是失败队伍的技术顾问
My brother Chase, who was technical adviser to the losing team.
这只是关于盲点的问题
He taught us that it's all about blind spots.
我知道你要去哪
I know where you're going!
还有 惊喜
And, uh, surprises.
小心点 伙计
Watch it, hobo.
为何你不看着我戴的手表
Why don't you watch the watch I'm wearing,
然后睡过去
the where of where you're watching, and sleep!
你要把骑士们 从飞机里扔出去
It's going to be your idea to throw the Horsemen out of the plane.
如果你还感到迷惑不解
If all of this is kind of confusing to you,
我可以之后向你解释
I can maybe catch you up on it later.
怎么说呢？也许我们 过个三五年就见到了？
Probably see you what, three to five?
来吧 击掌吧 嘿 以牙还牙 兄弟
Come on, put it there. Hey! Tit for tat, bro!
基本上 我们让他们知道了一切
Basically, we showed them everything.
你们如何绑架我们 以及偷窃在你口袋里的芯片
How you kidnapped us to steal the very thing that is in your pocket right now.
你知道 这个东西
You know, this thing here,
也就是你所说的可以 用来整顿市场
which you said you could use to adjust markets,
操纵政府 监视任何人的东西
manipulate governments, and spy on whomever you choose.
还有 你说的
Also, you could, as you said,
可以控制民众的东西
control the public from outside the grid.
这些人杀人害命
These men destroy people's lives.
监视整个世界 侵犯你们的隐私权
Spying on the world, robbing you of your right to privacy.
他们藏在黑暗中做着这一切
And they do that by hiding in the dark.
所以 根据骑士的传统 我们要揭发它们
So, in the Horsemen tradition, we're here to expose them.
今晚 他们 和我们大家一样
Tonight, they, like all of us,
终于站到了光亮处
are finally stepping into the light.
谢谢大家
Thank you, everybody!
我们是骑士 我们很快会再见
We are the Horsemen and we will be back very soon!
五 四 三 二 一
Five, four, three, two, one!
- 嘿 我们赶时间 - 快走
- Hey, we're on the clock. - Get a move on.
他们在哪里
There they are!
- 里面还有更多 - 你别碰我
- There's more inside. - Don't you bloody touch me!
骑士们就在…
The Horsemen are over on the…
见鬼
Oh, shit!
你呆在这
Stay with them!
所有人散开
Everybody spread out!
都别离开驳船
Nobody leaves this barge!
罗兹 站住 不许动
Rhodes, hold it right there! Do not move!
这里面包含了一切
This contains everything.
不仅仅是沃尔特和特雷斯勒的事 还有他们所有的交易
Not just Walter and Tressler, but all their dealings.
他们所有的连络人 整个的生意网络
All their contacts, the entire network.
我为什么要相信你？
And why on Earth would I believe you?
我告诉过你 我一直都是那样的人
I told you. I'm the same man I've always been.
快走 快点 走走走
Move it! Come on! Let's go, go, go!
我不是这个组织的成员 我是梅里特
I'm not part of this organization! I'm Merritt.
我被骗了 我被骗了
Rm a patsy! rm a patsy!
十分钟
Ten minutes.
现在轮到你玩了
Now you're playing the long game.
爸爸 我保证我会处理好的
Dad, I promise you I will fix this.
你不行 别再叫我爸爸
You can't. Stop calling me dad.
我上过的女人太多了 根本不知道你是谁的
There were so many women, I have no idea whose bastard you are.
什么？
What?
- 怎么回事？- 没看到 不见了 跟我来
- What happened? - Thin air, gone. Come with me.
你说不见了是什么意思？活人不可能这样凭空消失的
What're you talking about, gone? People don't just disappear.
你应该知道他根本不会魔术
You realize that he doesn't actually have magical powers!
（格林威治天文台）
- 嘿 各位 - 嘿
- Hey, guys. - Hey!
- 见到你们真好 - 见到你真好 李
- Good to see you all. - Good to see you, Li.
进来吧
Come on in.
早上好 欢迎
Good morning. Welcome.
我为你骄傲 为你们骄傲
I'm proud of you. All of you.
我有很多事要告诉你 来吧
I have a lot to show you. Come.
来吧
Come.
爸爸
Dad.
是的
Yes.
你父亲和我曾是搭档
Your father and I were partners.
我们的表演充满竞争力
Our act was that of rivals.
我是个坚定的现实主义者 而他是爱做梦的理想主义者
I was the hard-eyed realist. He was the dreamy-eyed idealist.
我们认为那是最好的组合
We thought it was the perfect misdirect.
是的 在公开场合 我刺激他
Yes, in public, I did goad him.
只是我们当时没想到 事情会闹得这么大
The only thing we didn't count on was it going so wrong.
为何？
Why?
为何你从来不和我说？
Why didn't you ever say anything to me?
我不知道
I don't know.
你想吧
Give it a name.
因为羞耻 内疚 后悔
Shame, guilt. Regret.
嘿 各位 你们也许想看看这个
Hey, guys, uh, you might wanna come take a look at this.
看啊
Look.
我把你送进监狱了 伙计
I put you in jail, man.
你当时为何不说些什么？
Why didn't you say something then?
你知道 我本来要说的
Well, you know, I was going to.
但你之后很快表现出了动机
But then, you were so quick to show your personal motivations that…
说实话 我被骗到了
Well, quite frankly it spoiled the trick for me.
我表现出了我的弱点
I showed my weakness.
这证明你没准备好
Well, it showed you weren't ready.
但是当你回到我的牢房
But when you came back to my cell,
你就已经放下了你对我 长达30年的仇恨
you had let go of your 30-year vendetta against me…
为了你的骑士
…for your Horsemen.
然后我对自己说 「那才是莱昂内尔的孩子」
And I said to myself, "That's Lionel's boy."
于是我就知道 见证他
And I knew it was my job to see to it
成为一名伟大的魔术师是我的责任
that he became the magician he was born to be.
所以剩下的就是…
All that was left then was…
让我知道真相
For me to hit bottom.
那么那保险箱 我父亲的手表 都是你安排的？
So the safe, my father's wristwatch, that was all you?
沃尔特和特雷斯勒也包括在内？
Walter and Tressler, were they in on it too?
我们知道沃尔特藏起来了
Oh, we knew Walter was in hiding.
演出只是为了让 公众知道他的存在
The Octa show was a setup to expose him to the public.
你对于骑士的想法是对的
And you were right about the Horsemen.
他们得学会像个 有机的整体一样合作
They needed to learn to work together like a single organism.
现在我知道 你为何看来如此眼熟了
Now I know why you look so familiar.
你是骑士 对吧？
You're the Horsemen, aren't you?
好
Okay.
但是事情不可能这么简单
But that can't be what all this is about.
你知道 最好的戏法 有着很多的标准
You know, the best tricks work on many levels.
其中最高深的一层 至少对我来说
And the deepest one, for me, at least,
就是此时此刻
is this moment right here.
我很抱歉 迪伦
I'm sorry, Dylan.
我想念你父亲
I miss your father.
30年的时间可不短 对吧？
Thirty years is a long time to drag something around, isn't it?
是的 没错
Yes, it is.
那么 现在怎么办？
So, now what?
- 现在我想退休了 - 喔
- Now I'm about out of moves. - Oh…
我累了
And I'm tired.
拜托 你可是说过要把
Come on, you're the one who said that you believe that this road
那些伟大的戏法破解的
led to the great wizard behind the curtain.
是啊
I did.
还有你终于能当面看清他
And that you'd finally get to look him in the eyes.
是的
I am.
现在到你了
It's your game now.
随你怎么去做
You play it however you see fit.
但我还是建议 你给自己找个继承人
My suggestion, however, is that you find yourself a successor.
嗨 好的 那么…
Hi. Okay, so, um…
显然我们有些问题 对吧？
Well, obviously, we have a few questions. Right?
呃 他说的几个 大概指的是五百万个
Uh… By "a few, " I think he means, like, five million.
- 是的 - 好吧
- Yeah. - Well.
祝你们好运
Good luck to you all.
- 好的 看到没 那不公平 - 什么
- Okay. See, that's not fair. - What!
- 拜托 - 那样不对
- Come on. - That's not right.
那样我会很生气的
That's gonna make me really angry!
现在不行
Not right now.
哦 对了…
Oh, um, by the way…
不要在意那幕布
Pay no attention to the curtain.
那里有幕布
There is a curtain.
走 走
Go, go!
眼见为实 但这是真的吗？
Seeing is believing. But is it truth?
这要看你从哪个角度去看
Depends on your point of view.
你们在听吗 骑士们？
Are you listening, Horsemen?
当你们出现 你们会出现的
When you emerge, and you will,
我会在那等着
I will be there waiting.
因为记住我的话 你们会得到应得的
Because mark my words, you will get what's coming to you
只是过程让你们无法预料
in ways you can't expect.
但那是你们应得的
But very much deserve.
因为我相信一件事
Because one thing I believe in
以眼还眼
is an eye for an eye.